<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Best-Of on iCosmoGeek</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/categories/best-of/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Best-Of on iCosmoGeek</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.140.2</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2013 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/categories/best-of/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How To Wake Your PC From Sleep Automatically</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2013-05-23-how-to-wake-your-pc-from-sleep-automatically/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2013-05-23-how-to-wake-your-pc-from-sleep-automatically/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Have you ever wondered whether you can wake up your PC automatically without actually pressing the power button? This can be useful in scenarios where you want to perform heavy downloads in off-peak hours or other similar actions before you wake up in the morning, without running your computer all the night!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://iCosmoGeek.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/05/Sleep-PC.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Sleep PC&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;//localhost:1313/posts/2013-05-23-how-to-wake-your-pc-from-sleep-automatically/images/Sleep-PC.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.flickr.com/photos/strandell/2446408542/&#34;&gt;Credit&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Follow these step by step procedure to wake your PC from sleep automatically:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Step 1: Open &lt;strong&gt;Task Scheduler&lt;/strong&gt; by searching for it in Start Menu&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looks like, I&#39;m going with T-Mobile. $600 less than AT&amp;T, $1000 less than Sprint.</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2013-03-27-looks-like-im-going-with-t-mobile-600-less-than-att-1000-less-than-sprint/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2013-03-27-looks-like-im-going-with-t-mobile-600-less-than-att-1000-less-than-sprint/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As expected, T-Mobile finally lands the iPhone. That&amp;rsquo;s six years after Apple announced first game changing device. The company will start offering iPhone with LTE support starting from April 12, 2013. Now that iPhone (especially iPhone 5) is available on all major US carriers, which carrier offers the best deal? After careful breakdown, looks like, I&amp;rsquo;m going with T-Mobile down the lane after my contract ends with AT&amp;amp;T. T-Mobile is the clear winner on price — with a 16GB iPhone 5 and two years of service costing nearly $600 less than AT&amp;amp;T and Verizon and nearly $1000 less than Sprint.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Reset Domain Admin Password on Windows Server 2008 R2</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2013-01-23-how-to-reset-domain-admin-password-on-windows-server-2008-r2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2013-01-23-how-to-reset-domain-admin-password-on-windows-server-2008-r2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;One of my friends recently contacted me to help reset domain admin password on Windows Server 2008 R2 domain controller that I helped him set up a year back. There are many tools in the market which help resetting administrator password. In fact, most of them help in resetting local administrator password, but not domain administrator password.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is an easy way to reset your Domain Administrator password. All you need is a copy of the Windows Server 2008 R2 installation disk and one simple command line trick.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nokia Faked Its New Lumia 920 PureView Ad</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-09-06-nokia-faked-its-new-pureview-ad/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-09-06-nokia-faked-its-new-pureview-ad/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Earlier today, Nokia announced Lumia 920, which comes with PureView, the same technology which received a decent response for &lt;a href=&#34;http://icosmogeek.com/why-megapixels-dont-matter-and-nokias-41mp-phone-is-just-a-hype/&#34;&gt;41 MP Nokia 808  device&lt;/a&gt;. During its press event, Nokia gave a look at the new PureView’s main feature: optical image stabilization (OIS). The idea behind this new feature is that it stabilizes the video you’re recording, giving you a more professional look instead of the amateur shaky-cam effect. To demonstrate this technology, Nokia played an impressive ad which show cases a side by side comparison of the video shot without OIS and with OIS. Obviously, the video shot without OIS doesn’t look very good, whereas the video shot with OIS activated looks excellent. Strangely, Nokia faked this PureView ad!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shame on Siri - Google Brings Enhanced Voice Search To iPhones And iPads</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-08-09-google-wants-to-kill-siri-by-bringing-google-now-to-iphones-and-ipads/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-08-09-google-wants-to-kill-siri-by-bringing-google-now-to-iphones-and-ipads/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In an official blog post, Google announced today that it&amp;rsquo;s adding its enhanced voice powered search to its &amp;lsquo;Search App&amp;rsquo; for the iPhone and iPad. This update will include enhanced voice functionality which is similar to Google Now feature that&amp;rsquo;s already available for Jelly Bean users. This feature proved to give some prominent results in Android devices and  now Google is bringing this feature to iPhones and iPads to kill Siri.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Gates On India, China, Philanthropy, Technology and More</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-08-06-bill-gates-on-india-china-philanthropy-tech-industry-and-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-08-06-bill-gates-on-india-china-philanthropy-tech-industry-and-more/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this recent interview for Bloomberg&amp;rsquo;s Charlie Rose, Microsoft co-founder Bill Gates talks quite a bit about India, China relative to technology, Philanthropy, Technology industry, how US Politics slow down innovation and much more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Its worth to spend around one hour of your time watching this video which was aired in the first week of July on Bloomberg&amp;rsquo;s network.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://iCosmoGeek.com/bill-gates-on-india-china-philanthropy-tech-industry-and-more/bill-gates-on-philantropy-tech-industry/&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;//localhost:1313/posts/2012-08-06-bill-gates-on-india-china-philanthropy-tech-industry-and-more/images/Bill-Gates-on-Philantropy-Tech-Industry.jpg&#34; title=&#34;Bill Gates on Philantropy, Tech Industry&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The interview starts with an intro of Bill Gates on his &lt;a href=&#34;http://icosmogeek.com/bill-gates-on-why-he-went-to-india-recently/&#34;&gt;latest visit to India&lt;/a&gt;, what differs India from China relative to technology and his opinion of where each excels, etc. I have listed out some interesting from the video below:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 Things To Know About Ex-Googler, New Yahoo CEO Marissa Mayer</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-07-18-10-things-to-know-about-ex-googler-new-yahoo-ceo-marissa-mayer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-07-18-10-things-to-know-about-ex-googler-new-yahoo-ceo-marissa-mayer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Yesterday, Google&amp;rsquo;s first female engineer, Marissa Mayer, resigned. After spending 13 years at Google, she begins her career as Yahoo&amp;rsquo;s new CEO at the age of 37.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She is &amp;lsquo;product focused&amp;rsquo; and focused on the &amp;lsquo;user experience&amp;rsquo;. She is good at mentoring talent. At Google, she was responsible for Google&amp;rsquo;s popular products: the simple white search homepage, Gmail, Google News, and Google Images.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://iCosmoGeek.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/07/Marissa-Mayer-at-Chirp.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;//localhost:1313/posts/2012-07-18-10-things-to-know-about-ex-googler-new-yahoo-ceo-marissa-mayer/images/Marissa-Mayer-at-Chirp.jpg&#34; title=&#34;Marissa Mayer at Chirp&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.flickr.com/photos/jolieodell/4524497781/sizes/l/in/photostream/&#34;&gt;Credit&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not familiar with this newly appointmented CEO? Here are some of the interesting things to know about Marissa with some inputs from &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.geeksugar.com/Facts-About-Marissa-Mayer-Yahoo-CEO-24016600&#34;&gt;GeekSugar&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Set Chrome Browser As Default On iPhone, iPad, iPod Touch [Jailbreak &amp; Non-Jailbreak Tweaks]</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-06-29-how-to-set-chrome-browser-as-default-on-iphone-ipad-ipod-touch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-06-29-how-to-set-chrome-browser-as-default-on-iphone-ipad-ipod-touch/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Yesterday, Google &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/k_avinash/status/218436002560217088&#34;&gt;released&lt;/a&gt; &amp;lsquo;Chrome for iOS&amp;rsquo; and its already in Apple&amp;rsquo;s top charts downloads. This browser brings all of the awesome features especially the user interface, Google account sync, Incognito mode, etc. Clearly, its much better browser than iOS&amp;rsquo;s default Safari browser. Unfortunately, there is no option to set Chrome as default in your iOS device. This means by clicking any link will launch Safari by default and there is no such option to change. But, there is already a tweak which allows you to set Google Chrome as default browser on your iPhone, iPad or iPod Touch.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What You Need To Know About IPV6 Launch Day. Father of the Internet Discusses Why We Need It [Video]</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-06-05-what-you-need-to-know-about-ipv6-launch-day-father-of-the-internet-discusses-why-we-need-it-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-06-05-what-you-need-to-know-about-ipv6-launch-day-father-of-the-internet-discusses-why-we-need-it-video/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;On June 6, 2012, the world will change and its forever. Major Internet service providers (ISPs), home networking equipment manufacturers, and web companies around the world are coming together to permanently enable IPv6 for their products and services by tomorrow on World IPV6 launch day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To remind about this launch, Google posted a video of Vint Cerf who is called Father of the Internet and also a Chief Internet Evangelist at Google where he discusses the next version of IPV6 and why we need it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Brings Epic Ramayana In An Awesome Interactive Chrome Experiment</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-06-01-google-brings-epic-ramayana-in-an-awesome-interactive-chrome-experiment/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-06-01-google-brings-epic-ramayana-in-an-awesome-interactive-chrome-experiment/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Google Indonesia has created an awesome and pretty sweet Chrome experiment that tells the story of Ramayana in an interactive visualization in a digital way. The story is the same classic Sanskrit epic but the characters Ram, Sita, Ravan and Hanuman use modern Google tools like Google Talk, Maps, G+, Docs, Weather, Gmail, Product search and other Google tools in this showcase. As the story goes on, Jatayu even writes a blog!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Stream Live On YouTube via Google&#43; On Air</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-05-14-how-to-stream-live-on-youtube-via-google-on-air/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-05-14-how-to-stream-live-on-youtube-via-google-on-air/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Google+ now allows you to live broadcast your video on air and simultaneously on YouTube with just few simple steps. You can stream your content publicly on your Google+ profile, your YouTube channel and also on your blog/website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The feature is called Hangouts On Air, which has been available to selected users for a while, but is only now being released for general use. The ability to use Hangouts On Air will be rolling out to everyone over the next few weeks. You can also plan to stream your content like birthday, marriage or other occasions. As of now, this will broadcast publicly everything.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just How Big Is Apple? [Infographic]</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-05-10-just-how-big-is-apple-infographic/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-05-10-just-how-big-is-apple-infographic/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Just imagine how Apple is really worth in terms of cash? Apple&amp;rsquo;s total sales in 2011 alone were $128 billion! That&amp;rsquo;s more than the gross domestic product of about 160 nations around the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://iCosmoGeek.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/05/white-apple.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;How Big is Apple&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;//localhost:1313/posts/2012-05-10-just-how-big-is-apple-infographic/images/white-apple.jpg&#34; title=&#34;white-apple&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is an interesting infographic from &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.bestcomputersciencedegrees.com/apple/&#34;&gt;Best Computer Science Degrees&lt;/a&gt; which compares Apple&amp;rsquo;s massive reach around the world. Some of the eye-popping statistics of the trillion dollar company -&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Apple&amp;rsquo;s release of its latest iPad was massive: the company sold 3 million devices in the first 72 hours of release.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Drive or Microsoft SkyDrive or Dropbox? Which is Right for Me?</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-04-26-google-drive-or-microsoft-skydrive-or-dropbox-which-is-right-for-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-04-26-google-drive-or-microsoft-skydrive-or-dropbox-which-is-right-for-me/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Its cloud storage everywhere! You have your files, pictures, videos on your home or office computer that you would like to access from other locations on different devices while on the go. Or you want to maintain a copy of all your data on somewhere on the Internet as a backup so that you can quickly access them from anywhere. This is where the cloud storage is useful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dropbox has been the leading cloud storage vendor from long time but this may change soon as the software giants Microsoft and Google entered the market with the launch of SkyDrive and Google Drive (&lt;em&gt;it just launched yesterday&lt;/em&gt;) respectively.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Can&#39;t Afford a Mac — What is the Next Best?</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-04-24-i-cant-afford-a-mac-what-is-the-next-best/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-04-24-i-cant-afford-a-mac-what-is-the-next-best/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Macs have generally been the forerunner when it comes to computers and tablets, which is why so many people have purchased iMacs, Macbook Pros and iPads. And while these computers and these tablets have an array of great features, have a great support group, and will not become infected with a virus, some people simply cannot afford their hefty price tags. Rather than considering yourself unlucky to not own a Mac product, there are other options out there that can mimic the Macs—and they can do this with a much lower purchase price.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can We Trust Google? [Infographic]</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-04-18-can-we-trust-google-infographic/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-04-18-can-we-trust-google-infographic/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Your day begins with a wakeup call from your Android phone, Google News, then Gmail, Calendar for appointments, Maps for direction to reach your destination. You use Transaltor if you find something interesting that is not in your native language. You use Docs for creating spreadsheets at work, use Google Groups for discussions and spend on Google search rest of the day!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Google has become part of our life. Its an interesting question everyone should consider to ask how much of your life does Google own? Popular services like Gmail, Gtalk, Reader, YouTube, Maps, Calendar, Contacts and of course Search shows everything Google &amp;lsquo;owns&amp;rsquo; your life!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How an iPad is Made? [Video]</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-04-16-how-an-ipad-is-made-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-04-16-how-an-ipad-is-made-video/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maketplace&amp;rsquo;s Shanghai Chief Rob Schmitz found his way into the factories of Apple&amp;rsquo;s Chinese producer, Foxconn. Rob recently granted an extremely rare opportunity to visit the factory floor and he is only the second reporter to be allowed till date.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Foxconn is the largest manufacturer of electronics an computer components in the world. Foxconn produces several common consumer electronics including the Mac mini, the iPod, iPad, and iPhone, Dell, HP, Playstation 2 and 3, Wii, Xbox, Motorola, Nokia, and the Amazon Kindle.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>cosmoGeek.info is Dead...Long Live iCosmoGeek.com!</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-04-15-cosmogeek-info-is-dead-long-live-icosmogeek-com/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-04-15-cosmogeek-info-is-dead-long-live-icosmogeek-com/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today is a big day for this blog! After blogging for over 2 years under the domain name &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cosmoGeek.info&#34;&gt;www.cosmoGeek.info&lt;/a&gt;, I have decided to make a strategic move and change the domain name to &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.iCosmoGeek.com&#34;&gt;www.iCosmoGeek.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I started blogging 2 years ago, I had no idea it would get this big. Today is very emotional day for me. I feel like I&amp;rsquo;m seeing this blog future ahead. I have all those good memories running in my mind. I am excited and I am incredibly proud of what I have accomplished out of this blog as of now. But there is lot more to do.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Megapixels Don’t Matter And Nokia’s 41MP Phone Is Just A Hype</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-03-09-why-megapixels-dont-matter-and-nokias-41mp-phone-is-just-a-hype/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-03-09-why-megapixels-dont-matter-and-nokias-41mp-phone-is-just-a-hype/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Everybody surprised during last month’s Mobile Congress 2012 event where Nokia announced the world’s first phone with a massive 41 megapixel camera. This resolution in fact tops most DSLRs and the professional high-end cameras. Well, megapixels don’t matter at all after a certain point. Read on…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh3.ggpht.com/-WLrBMS74Cx8/T1puvQVvJgI/AAAAAAAAIeo/PPOnGZsZD1s/s1600-h/image3.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Nokia 808 PureView&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh5.ggpht.com/-Qg48ximOQOo/T1puv_gnNzI/AAAAAAAAIew/gvvJyYMpR74/image_thumb1.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;Nokia 808 PureView&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before discussing about the latest Nokia phone hype, read what exactly a megapixel (MP or Mpx) from &lt;a href=&#34;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pixel#Megapixel&#34;&gt;Wikipedia&lt;/a&gt; -&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“A megapixel (MP or Mpx) is one million pixels, and is a term used not only for the number of pixels in an image, but to express the number of image sensor elements of digital cameras or the number of display elements of digital displays. For example, a camera that makes a 2048 × 1536 pixel image typically uses a few extra rows and columns of sensor elements and is commonly said to have &amp;ldquo;3.2 megapixels&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;3.3 megapixels&amp;rdquo;, depending on whether the number reported is the &amp;ldquo;effective&amp;rdquo; or the &amp;ldquo;total&amp;rdquo; pixel count (as opposed to the 2048 × 1536 = 3,145,728 finished image pixels).”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Apple Actually Named The new iPad as ‘The new iPad’</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-03-08-why-apple-actually-named-the-new-ipad-as-the-new-ipad/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-03-08-why-apple-actually-named-the-new-ipad-as-the-new-ipad/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Finally, Apple released its next iPad few hours ago. Before Apple’s event today, there were number of speculations that this ‘Resolutionary’ (&lt;em&gt;that’s what Apple is calling it on its official&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.apple.com/ipad/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;website&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;)  device is called as ‘iPad 3’ or ‘iPad HD’. But, Apple just named this new product as just ‘&lt;strong&gt;The new iPad’&lt;/strong&gt;. Perfect!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh4.ggpht.com/-mXBy_2uLv2s/T1f8E1aJl2I/AAAAAAAAIeY/0vTGlQVvm_Y/s1600-h/image%25255B3%25255D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;The new iPad&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh3.ggpht.com/-g9F22aGJB6s/T1f8Fu-dW3I/AAAAAAAAIeg/a47oFR4rJ-k/image_thumb%25255B1%25255D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;The new iPad&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This naming convention makes sense if you think for long term. Just think about in future, does iPhone 13 or iPad 16 makes sense to you? This also makes sense if you think about the iPhone series. The current iPhone 4S is actually the fifth generation iPhone device, and the next iPhone series is the sixth generation and Apple may call it as iPhone 5. Err, may be or completely not. Hope Apple call the next iPhone just ‘iPhone’, instead of iPhone 5. This is just similar to MacBooks, iMacs or Apple TVs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why iPad Leads the Tablet Market and Internet Usage?</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-02-29-why-ipad-leads-the-tablet-market-and-internet-usage/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-02-29-why-ipad-leads-the-tablet-market-and-internet-usage/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As we stepped into 2012 we saw a number of tablet computers launched at the Consumer Electronic Show (CES) held at the Las Vegas Convention Center last month. Almost a hundred new tablets were launched at the CES last year in different sizes, specifications, operating systems, etc. with the introduction of pressure sensors. This year we saw fairly the same amounts of tablets released with a wave of tablets using the Android and Windows operating systems.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Service Your Own Computer</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-02-24-how-to-service-your-own-computer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-02-24-how-to-service-your-own-computer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Believe it or not, it is possible to service a computer from home. The best part is that it will only take around fifteen minutes a month to do so, but it will benefit the user in the long run as it will keep the computer stable, safe and optimized.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-Yxsr7xKFpNc/T0cSOsph9fI/AAAAAAAAIcA/Dvj_YbNaydI/s1600/6713719679_b3f57a2da8.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;//localhost:1313/posts/2012-02-24-how-to-service-your-own-computer/images/6713719679_b3f57a2da8.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is a checklist of the things that can be done on a regular basis, all of which are completely free of charge:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weird Gadgets To Gift On This Valentine&#39;s Day: Go Wacky!</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-02-09-weird-gadgets-to-gift-on-this-valentines-day-go-wacky/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-02-09-weird-gadgets-to-gift-on-this-valentines-day-go-wacky/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you have a geeky boyfriend or girlfriend and you really find it tough to impress him/her with the conventional roses, chocolates and teddies, then try something wacky that will get them noticing you and the gift in no time!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are some weird gadgets that your beau is sure to adore this Valentines:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. The &amp;lsquo;Control Your Spouse&amp;rsquo; talking remote&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
This talking remote will surely have your man or woman cracking up with the verbal one-off sounds and effects that will put your spouse back on track! Now the famous one-liners can be belted out with the help of a button mimicking the popular &amp;ldquo;What were you thinking?&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;What about my needs?&amp;rdquo; or the &amp;ldquo;All right, hand over the credit cards!&amp;rdquo; and many more! You could buy this talking remote in either male or female varieties - which will make your love, think of you all the time!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Screenshots of Newly Jailbroken iPhone 4S [Updated]</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-02-05-screenshots-of-newly-jailbroken-iphone-4s-updated/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-02-05-screenshots-of-newly-jailbroken-iphone-4s-updated/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For the past four months, I&amp;rsquo;ve used a &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/2011/10/iphone-4s-unboxing-pictures.html&#34;&gt;stock iPhone 4S&lt;/a&gt;. That was not my choice as there wasn&amp;rsquo;t a jailbreak for iPhone 4S. Today, I&amp;rsquo;ve jailbroken my iPhone 4S to experience the magic of Cydia!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You are probably thinking – why should you consider jailbreaking your device? Some simple reasons are mentioned &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/2010/09/6-simple-reasons-to-jailbreak-your.html&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; despite many.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First day screenshots from my new device -&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Notification Center -&lt;/strong&gt; Notice the ‘Superman’ logo replacing the official carrier logo. Date, Time, free memory in the status bar. Instant call, One touch twitter, search google, spy cam, and more – all from the notification center&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 Things Android Can Do Better Than iPhone</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-02-04-20-things-android-can-do-better-than-iphone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-02-04-20-things-android-can-do-better-than-iphone/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The very first iPhone was launched on the 29th July 2007 and on that day, the world of mobile phones changed for ever. Other cell phone manufacturers cowered, whispering amongst themselves. No single phone blew its horn in challenge. And then came &lt;strong&gt;Android&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh5.ggpht.com/-3n6Nb17bOxM/TyzX-GawdUI/AAAAAAAAIV8/7p0hH3pEGGk/s1600-h/4742571766_37a4d7bddb_b%25255B3%25255D.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Android&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh3.ggpht.com/-QU70ErHcJ_s/TyzX-vvYZkI/AAAAAAAAIWE/ndjcQgZDlkw/4742571766_37a4d7bddb_b_thumb%25255B1%25255D.jpg?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;Android&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And today we are actually talking about 20 things that Android can do better than iPhones!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Android Supports Multiple Hardware Options&lt;/strong&gt; About 10 brands of smartphones use Android OS at the moment, and the list is growing. iOS, on the other hand, is used only by iPhones and other Apple devices.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 Awesome iPhone Apps for Women</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-02-03-5-awesome-iphone-apps-for-women/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-02-03-5-awesome-iphone-apps-for-women/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Everyone has heard about how great &lt;strong&gt;iPhones&lt;/strong&gt; are. They have apps, or applications, for just about anything you could need, they can communicate over wi-fi, and they can have as much memory and processing power as a laptop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Business executives use them to keep track of companies and teenagers use them to text and surf the Internet. While iphones have uses for almost everyone, there are certain features which make them especially useful for women.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airbags For iPhone: It’s Worth Every Penny</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-01-31-airbags-for-iphone-its-worth-every-penny/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-01-31-airbags-for-iphone-its-worth-every-penny/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The recent drop test conducted by Apple for iPhones proved that these devices are pretty delicate as compared to the other Smartphones in the market. The drop test conducted on iPhone proved the fact that the glass cover easily breaks once the device falls down. However, Apple has embarked with an interesting kind of solution by introducing a new &lt;strong&gt;airbag&lt;/strong&gt; for iPhone, iPad and iPad touch. This bag will assure a right kind of safety to these named devices. Besides, the company is also seen taking measures to work on the durability factor of these products. By this move the company is leaving no stone unturned to allow the consumers to opt the rival Smartphones.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Make Extra Money Using Craigslist</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-01-25-how-to-make-extra-money-using-craigslist/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-01-25-how-to-make-extra-money-using-craigslist/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you’re looking to make some extra cash, you might want to try turning your efforts toward Craigslist’s local and free online classified ads. &lt;a href=&#34;http://craigslist.org/&#34;&gt;Craigslist&lt;/a&gt; has been around for a while, but it’s still a place that many people frequent. It’s a great place to meet people in your community for group activities or mutual interests, find or post a job, and buy or sell just about anything at all. If you use it correctly, you can find some great opportunities to earn some extra spending money. Start by signing up for a free account and finding your local page. There are Craigslist sites for hundreds of cities and regions across the country, so find the one or two closest to your location and get started.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>External Hard Drives For Your iPad or Android Tablet</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-01-24-external-hard-drives-for-your-ipad-or-android-tablet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-01-24-external-hard-drives-for-your-ipad-or-android-tablet/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It’s raining tablets and smart phones everywhere. They all are packed with never heard of features and that too in real small packs. But a major drawback of any tablet or smart phone is its limited storage capacity. Even the top of the class devices cannot carry too many movies or audios. Those with expandable memories are too limited by inadequacy of flash drives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It seems hard drives would have been a better way out. And Seagate cared to come out with a solution. They released an external hard drive - GoFlex Satellite - capable of streaming data to iPads, Android tablets and even smartphones.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web Goes On Strike On Jan 18 Along With Wikipedia Shutdown</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-01-17-web-goes-on-strike-on-jan-18-along-with-wikipedia-shutdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-01-17-web-goes-on-strike-on-jan-18-along-with-wikipedia-shutdown/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This Wednesday, January 18, Wikipedia is going offline for 24 hours in protest of the &lt;strong&gt;Stop Online Piracy Act (SOPA).&lt;/strong&gt; While Wikipedia &lt;a href=&#34;http://wikimediafoundation.org/wiki/Press_releases/English_Wikipedia_to_go_dark&#34;&gt;announced&lt;/a&gt; that only the English version of the site will be offline, it could effect almost 25 million average visitors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Along with Wikipedia, big Internet names like Reddit, WordPress, Mozilla joins the black out protest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh5.ggpht.com/-gIgaBdz3fP0/TxUwqI1LT_I/AAAAAAAAIGw/kMr4-YPdT4o/s1600-h/image%25255B2%25255D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh4.ggpht.com/-QYZHWt3lm78/TxUwqgcElWI/AAAAAAAAIG4/EQflHfc-l3Y/image_thumb.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, what is this Stop Online Piracy Act (SOPA) all about? Before checking all those Facebook statuses, Twitter for SOPA, check it out this short video by Fight &lt;a href=&#34;http://fightforthefuture.org/&#34;&gt;For the Future&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Extend the Life of Your Laptop’s Battery</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-01-09-how-to-extend-the-life-of-your-laptops-battery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-01-09-how-to-extend-the-life-of-your-laptops-battery/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Your laptop’s just as good as how much battery power you have left, especially if you use it unplugged a lot. There is, of course, the option of leaving your laptop plugged in most of the time, but mobility - the main reason to get a laptop - does require you to be unplugged from time to time. And during these periods, you certainly will want to extend the life of your battery for as long as possible. The good news is that there are many practical things that you can do to make the most of whatever power you have in your laptop battery. Apply these tips and enjoy your laptop for a longer time without having to scramble around looking for a socket.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>cosmoGeek: Best of 2011</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-01-01-cosmogeek-best-of-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2012-01-01-cosmogeek-best-of-2011/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Good bye 2011! You won’t be missed in my life!! To write this last article for this year, I managed to combine most of the articles that are best of 2011 in this post. Sit back and read all these best articles on &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/&#34;&gt;cosmoGeek&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; and cheers 2012!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh3.ggpht.com/-NzGvBiXsCSQ/Tv-tbTXC3XI/AAAAAAAAIBE/am_yGCwN72Y/s1600-h/image%25255B2%25255D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh5.ggpht.com/-8f7YRgYOmrI/Tv-tcMelK6I/AAAAAAAAIBM/dEtccXWESxg/image_thumb.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;January 2011&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/2011/01/google-releases-android-30-honeycomb.html&#34;&gt;Google releases Android 3.0 Honeycomb video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/2011/01/is-ipod-really-that-much-greater-than.html&#34;&gt;Is the iPod Really That Much Greater than a Regular MP3 Player?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/2011/01/whats-new-in-ios-43.html&#34;&gt;What’s New in iOS 4.3?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/2011/01/print-from-anywhere-using-google-cloud.html&#34;&gt;Print From Anywhere Using Google Cloud Print&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;February 2011&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Favorite iPhone Apps for Your Car</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-12-30-7-favorite-iphone-apps-for-your-car/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-12-30-7-favorite-iphone-apps-for-your-car/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you have an iPhone or an Android device, you’ve got apps. Games, organizers, calendars and various trackers can be found on virtually any mobile device. But do you have apps for your car? There are tons of apps for drivers; some are free and some will cost you but they are all useful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-erYlFwAFpL4/Tv1ZgVdrlOI/AAAAAAAAIA8/oV_Z3KoSsk0/s1600/2011-12-30_002542.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;//localhost:1313/posts/2011-12-30-7-favorite-iphone-apps-for-your-car/images/2011-12-30_002542.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are our favorites:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;G-Park&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While it can be difficult to lose your car in the parking lot of an amusement park with their lot markers and landmarks, it is incredibly easy to misplace your car at the mall. If you frequently find yourself wandering through parking lot aisles searching fruitlessly for your car, this app is for you. When you exit your car, hit the ‘Park’ button and when you’re ready to find it, hit the ‘Where did I park?’ button. The app will guide you to your parking spot. Handy!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Insert Your Profile Picture As Emoticon In Facebook Chat</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-12-29-how-to-insert-your-profile-picture-as-emoticon-in-facebook-chat/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-12-29-how-to-insert-your-profile-picture-as-emoticon-in-facebook-chat/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For all those Facebook chat fans, here is a cool trick to insert your profile picture as emoticon inside chat windows. In fact, this trick works with any of the profile pictures, Facebook pages. This means you can insert Mark Zuckerberg’s face or even Jessica Alba’s picture while chatting with your friends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/-gOL13j5hZVE/TvwLR8qe5sI/AAAAAAAAIAo/3HUID0y_Jeg/s1600-h/image%25255B8%25255D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh3.ggpht.com/-FemTtPVkSCo/TvwLSGDO_LI/AAAAAAAAIAw/JLRbdC2MBQI/image_thumb%25255B4%25255D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As shown in the above picture (leave those red rectangles), you can insert profile pictures of Facebook users and also pages inside chat windows.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Convert YouTube Videos To MP3 Format</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-12-24-how-to-convert-youtube-videos-to-mp3-format/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-12-24-how-to-convert-youtube-videos-to-mp3-format/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;YouTube to mp3 websites are wonderful tools for anyone who enjoys listening to their music on YouTube and want it in mp3 format. In the digital age, it is certainly not unusual for people to see a video on YouTube that features great music they would love to have in their own personal collection. However, you cannot simply download a video and automatically get it in mp3 format. This is where conversion websites that provide a service comes handy.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iPad vs. Kindle vs. Nook: Which One Should You Buy?</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-12-23-ipad-vs-kindle-vs-nook-which-one-should-you-buy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-12-23-ipad-vs-kindle-vs-nook-which-one-should-you-buy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So you finally gave in – you finally decided that it’s time to invest in an e-book reader.  But which one?  Apple’s iPad?  Amazon’s Kindle?  Noble’s Nook?  Choosing an e-reader may seem like an overwhelming task, but with the right information and the awareness of your particular needs, the choice should be a simpler one than you may think.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-eN8nq374Gb4/TvPHDw4jNGI/AAAAAAAAIAU/jopcs0YQq5E/s1600/Capture.JPG&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;//localhost:1313/posts/2011-12-23-ipad-vs-kindle-vs-nook-which-one-should-you-buy/images/Capture.JPG&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reader or tablet&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Are you looking for just a book reader, or do you want access to magazines and newspapers as well?  Do you want a device that allows you to browse the Internet, listen to music, and watch movies, or do you have your laptop for all of that?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inkjet vs. Laser Printers for Your Home Office</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-12-21-inkjet-vs-laser-printers-for-your-home-office/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-12-21-inkjet-vs-laser-printers-for-your-home-office/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Whether you’re a printer for your home office for the first time or just in need of a replacement, inkjet versus laser is a question that will be on your mind. Which should you choose? What is the best investment? The highest quality? Which is the right choice for you? There is no quick, easy answer to this question. When you’re trying to decide, you need to weigh a few different things concerning what you’ll be using the printer for. Each home business is different, and you’ll need to consider your own personal needs when deciding between an inkjet and laser printer.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HTC Android Phones Are Being Banned from the US. Apple Won Patent Effective April 2012</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-12-20-htc-android-phones-are-being-banned-from-the-us-apple-won-patent-effective-april-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-12-20-htc-android-phones-are-being-banned-from-the-us-apple-won-patent-effective-april-2012/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When Steve Jobs claimed that Google “stole” Apple’s innovation, today, the United States Trade Commission (ITC) agreed and all those HTC infringing products are banned from the US. This rule applies to several popular HTC products including Evo 4G, Droid Incredible, G2, etc. The rule applies to all Android HTC devices running 1.6 to 2.2 in the United States effective April 2012.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before reading all those long pages of patents and infringements, here is the main ‘copycat’ reason. &lt;a href=&#34;http://tech.fortune.cnn.com/2011/07/16/apple-vs-google-inside-an-android-patent-violation/&#34;&gt;CNN Fortune&lt;/a&gt; took an in-depth review of this patent and according to them, it works like this -&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Android Phone Is Recording Everything You Do. Really Bad.</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-11-30-your-android-phone-is-recording-everything-you-do-really-bad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-11-30-your-android-phone-is-recording-everything-you-do-really-bad/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We have seen many &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/2011/10/major-security-hole-discovered-in-htc.html&#34;&gt;security loop holes&lt;/a&gt; in Android related to either malware, apps, custom carrier modifications. Now, 25 year old Android developer Trevor Eckhart has discovered an interesting piece of software that comes pre-installed on most Android, Blackberry and Nokia phones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It records everything you do from your phone. It can even grab your passwords and queries! Worse!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/-T8pfSB2kAXM/TtairdLK45I/AAAAAAAAHww/jCV9omUnpJg/s1600-h/image%25255B3%25255D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh5.ggpht.com/-C6RlrEjvevQ/TtaisJ3-rmI/AAAAAAAAHw0/Sb_kuU-gFoU/image_thumb%25255B1%25255D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The below embedded video recorded by Trevor shows how it works. The spying software called &lt;strong&gt;Carrier IQ&lt;/strong&gt; (developed by &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.carrieriq.com&#34;&gt;www.carrieriq.com&lt;/a&gt;) secretly logs everything a user does with his phone including text messages, encrypted web searches, phone calls, location and you name as well!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 Best Mobile Apps for College Students</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-11-18-10-best-mobile-apps-for-college-students/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-11-18-10-best-mobile-apps-for-college-students/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A life in college is a life filled with adventure, responsibility, and new experiences. What better way to maximize your time, efforts, and abilities with the use of improving technologies in mobile apps? Whither in medical school, the arts, or &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.technology-colleges.info/&#34;&gt;technology colleges&lt;/a&gt;, students can benefit from the latest in mobile technology. Get organized, get ready, and get serious about your college experience with the Top Ten Mobile Apps for College Students.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Story Behind Siri, Its Name and Founder</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-11-12-the-story-behind-siri-its-name-and-founder/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-11-12-the-story-behind-siri-its-name-and-founder/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Since Apple’s iPhone 4S &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/2011/10/iphone-4s-unboxing-pictures.html&#34;&gt;launch&lt;/a&gt;, everyone has been talking about one awesome feature: &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/2011/10/siri-will-you-marry-me-video.html&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Siri&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt; Unlike Apple’s own innovations, Siri – the digital personal assistant wasn’t made by Apple.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Siri was founded in 2007 by Dag Kittlaus (CEO), Adam Cheyer (VP Engineering) and Tom Gruber (CTO/VP Design). Siri was originally developed as an iOS application available in the App Store and later acquired by Apple on April 28, 2010. It is now integrated part of iOS 5 and available only on iPhone 4S (taken from Wikipedia).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Battery Usage’ Overlap With ‘Manage Storage’ in iOS 5. UI Bug [Video]</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-11-07-battery-usage-overlap-with-manage-storage-in-ios-5-ui-bug-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-11-07-battery-usage-overlap-with-manage-storage-in-ios-5-ui-bug-video/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Apple is remarkable and popular to its minute design tweaks and improvements in terms of graphics and calligraphy. Today, I noticed a weird text overlap on my &lt;strong&gt;iPhone 4S&lt;/strong&gt; running &lt;strong&gt;iOS 5&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before you watch the video to reproduce on your devices, here is the screenshot of the bug:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh4.ggpht.com/-jPgvks8jSGI/TrdNkSFbYzI/AAAAAAAAGYE/6ukWhn7Yucs/s1600-h/image%25255B2%25255D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/image%25255B5%25255D.png&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh4.ggpht.com/-w_WrGHWhU6I/TrdNl56ZZ7I/AAAAAAAAGYc/PB5VaHwLoU4/image_thumb%25255B1%25255D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you carefully observe above two screenshots, the &lt;strong&gt;‘Battery Usage’&lt;/strong&gt; is overlapped with &lt;strong&gt;‘Manage Storage’&lt;/strong&gt; and the iCloud description is also repeated twice in the first screenshot.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steve’s Final Words: OH WOW. OH WOW. OH WOW</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-10-31-steves-final-words-oh-wow-oh-wow-oh-wow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-10-31-steves-final-words-oh-wow-oh-wow-oh-wow/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mona Simpson, an author, professor of English at the University of California and biological sister of Steve Jobs. In an October 16 Eulogy delivered for her brother at his memorial service at the Memorial Church of Stanford University, she told that her brother’s final words were &lt;strong&gt;“Oh wow. Oh wow. Oh wow.”&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh4.ggpht.com/-cWScxXSL54A/Tq3qpcNVfEI/AAAAAAAAGOU/X3Y24Y3Xqk8/s1600-h/image%25255B2%25255D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh3.ggpht.com/-O2af7s-guQQ/Tq3qqZfAv6I/AAAAAAAAGOc/PtOFrft7Lkg/image_thumb.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As published in &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.nytimes.com/2011/10/30/opinion/mona-simpsons-eulogy-for-steve-jobs.html?pagewanted=1&amp;amp;_r=2&#34;&gt;The New York Times&lt;/a&gt;, Mona remembered Steve she first learned about when she was 25. A lawyer had informed her that she had a rich and famous long-lost brother.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iPhone 4S / Canon DSLR 5D – 1080p Video Comparison</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-10-21-iphone-4s-canon-dslr-5d-1080p-video-comparison/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-10-21-iphone-4s-canon-dslr-5d-1080p-video-comparison/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Here is the biggie! A ‘fair’ test between the newly &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/2011/10/iphone-4s-unboxing-pictures.html&#34;&gt;launched&lt;/a&gt; amazing device from Apple, iPhone 4S and a professional grade Canon DSLR 5D MK II. Both the videos are taken at Full 1080p HD resolution.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Previously, we saw &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/2011/10/iphone-4s-camera-pictures-look.html&#34;&gt;some amazing pictures&lt;/a&gt; taken using the iPhone 4S’ powerful camera. Now, &lt;a href=&#34;http://vimeo.com/30606785&#34;&gt;Robino Films&lt;/a&gt; has done a quite good video comparison. Exposure, shutter speed, frame rate and picture style were matched as close as possible between the two cameras.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iPhone 4S Unboxing (Pictures)</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-10-14-iphone-4s-unboxing-pictures/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-10-14-iphone-4s-unboxing-pictures/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After an extremely months of waiting, my &lt;strong&gt;iPhone 4S&lt;/strong&gt; finally got into my hands this morning. I was so excited to stand in the Apple fanboy line to grab the device this morning!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I greeted and rushed to get this cute little gorgeous opened!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh4.ggpht.com/-WdOnHpJ_V0s/Tphj4iC1s2I/AAAAAAAAF30/PaIzjYXsV0E/s1600-h/2011-10-14%25252007.04.32%25255B3%25255D.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;2011-10-14 07.04.32&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/2011-10-14%25252007.57.49%25255B3%25255D.jpg&#34; title=&#34;2011-10-14 07.04.32&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;2011-10-14 07.57.49&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/2011-10-14%25252008.41.41%25255B3%25255D.jpg&#34; title=&#34;2011-10-14 07.57.49&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;2011-10-14 08.41.41&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/2011-10-14%25252008.42.19%25255B3%25255D.jpg&#34; title=&#34;2011-10-14 08.41.41&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;2011-10-14 08.42.19&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/photo%2525202%252520%2525282%252529%25255B3%25255D.jpg&#34; title=&#34;2011-10-14 08.42.19&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;photo 2 (2)&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/2011-10-14%25252010.50.08%25255B3%25255D.jpg&#34; title=&#34;photo 2 (2)&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;2011-10-14 10.50.08&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/2011-10-14%25252010.52.38%25255B3%25255D.jpg&#34; title=&#34;2011-10-14 10.50.08&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;2011-10-14 10.52.38&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/2011-10-14%25252010.55.49%25255B3%25255D.jpg&#34; title=&#34;2011-10-14 10.52.38&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;2011-10-14 10.55.49&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh4.ggpht.com/-36IyHyzWmgc/TphkCAwL2FI/AAAAAAAAF5s/uPQh4LKX4Hk/2011-10-14%25252010.55.49_thumb.jpg?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;2011-10-14 10.55.49&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stay tuned, I have much more iPhone 4(Steve) content to come!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steve Jobs on Why He Wore Black Mock Turtleneck Uniform</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-10-11-steve-jobs-on-why-he-wore-black-mock-turtleneck-uniform/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-10-11-steve-jobs-on-why-he-wore-black-mock-turtleneck-uniform/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Do you ever even wonder how the consistent style of Steve Jobs’ black mock turtleneck uniform emerged? Before he &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/2011/10/thank-you-steve-rest-in-peace.html&#34;&gt;died&lt;/a&gt;, Steve himself explained to biographer &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/2011/10/steve-jobs-movie-is-coming-soon.html&#34;&gt;Walter Isaacson&lt;/a&gt;. This official biography is set to release on October 24th.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/-81sKUK9SWpk/TpSx4IcZn-I/AAAAAAAAF3k/mPG4AH7HHQ4/s1600-h/image%25255B2%25255D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh4.ggpht.com/-_klb8pvRUdM/TpSx4qFJhwI/AAAAAAAAF3s/90MbwLut7is/image_thumb.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The author Isaacson sent the real story behind the black turtleneck uniform to &lt;a href=&#34;http://gawker.com/5848754/steve-jobs-on-why-he-wore-turtlenecks&#34;&gt;Gawker&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;On a trip to Japan in the early 1980s, Jobs asked Sony&amp;rsquo;s chairman Akio Morita why everyone in the company&amp;rsquo;s factories wore uniforms. He told Jobs that after the war, no one had any clothes, and companies like Sony had to give their workers something to wear each day. Over the years, the uniforms developed their own signatures styles, especially at companies such as Sony, and it became a way of bonding workers to the company. &amp;ldquo;I decided that I wanted that type of bonding for Apple,&amp;rdquo; Jobs recalled.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iPhone 4S Camera Pictures Look Absolutely Stunning</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-10-05-iphone-4s-camera-pictures-look-absolutely-stunning/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-10-05-iphone-4s-camera-pictures-look-absolutely-stunning/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Apple posted some sample shots taken using the iPhone 4S’ powerful camera which was &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/2011/10/iphone-4s-a5-dual-core-8-mp-camera.html&#34;&gt;announced&lt;/a&gt; yesterday. In the official Apple’s website, Apple states that these photos are &lt;strong&gt;unretouched&lt;/strong&gt; which means that they weren’t altered with any photo editing software after being taken.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to Apple, this 8 megapixels and all-new optics camera might be the best camera ever on a mobile phone. Needless to say, these pictures are absolutely stunning. A real competitor to DSLR camera?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Want to Keep Your Job? 5 Facebook Statuses to Steer Clear of</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-10-01-want-to-keep-your-job-5-facebook-statuses-to-steer-clear-of/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-10-01-want-to-keep-your-job-5-facebook-statuses-to-steer-clear-of/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sure, Facebook is a great tool to use when you are updating your family members, or keeping in touch with your friends. Or, as some students put it, “Facebook Stalk” their friends. It&amp;rsquo;s great to upload pictures, chat with longtime friends that life faraway, and write on people&amp;rsquo;s walls. Sometimes, going on Facebook is also a great break. It could be a great break from a long homework assignment, or it can also be a good break from your work. Let&amp;rsquo;s face it, people can&amp;rsquo;t work 8 long hours without some sort of break. Going on Facebook is considered an acceptable form of a break. It can break the monotony. However, there are also some things that need to be considered when you go on Facebook.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Install Windows 8 on a Virtual Machine</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-09-15-how-to-install-windows-8-on-a-virtual-machine/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-09-15-how-to-install-windows-8-on-a-virtual-machine/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Now that Microsoft released Windows 8 Developer Preview build officially this Tuesday, want to see and test all new features right from your machine without disturbing existing operating system? Read on..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Interesting part about Windows 8 is that Microsoft is foreseeing an OS that scales right from small form factors, tablets and all the way to big servers. Major updates in this new operating system include Tablet Optimization, Picture Password, New Start Screen with ‘Tile’ (apps), Metro UI, Charms, IE 10.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Get Rid of “Facebook T-Shirt” Spam</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-09-09-how-to-get-rid-of-facebook-t-shirt-spam/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-09-09-how-to-get-rid-of-facebook-t-shirt-spam/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Are you one of those poor Facebook users who ended up clicking the latest scam of a &lt;strong&gt;free Facebook T-shirt?&lt;/strong&gt; Well, if you’re still hoping that you’re going to receive a free Tee, good luck by the way! You won’t receive one.&lt;br&gt;
This latest scam pretends you to claim a free Facebook Tee with an attractive webpage celebrating the social giant’s 7th birthday and saying it has more than 1.9 million official Tees in stock.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREAKING: Steve Jobs Resigns as Apple CEO. Tim Cook to Replace</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-08-25-breaking-steve-jobs-resigns-as-apple-ceo-tim-cook-to-replace/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-08-25-breaking-steve-jobs-resigns-as-apple-ceo-tim-cook-to-replace/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am very sorry to say that the most innovating icon in this world, Steve Jobs is stepping down as Apple&amp;rsquo;s CEO with effective immediately. He suggested COO Tim Cook to replace him who has been carrying out most of the operations over last several months. Even though he officially resigned, Jobs will still be actively involved in Apple&amp;rsquo;s future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/zrclip001n473ade1.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I could go on and write about Steve&amp;rsquo;s innovations, revolutions and accomplishments but I recommend to read the official &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/2011/04/steve-jobs-official-biography-coming-in.html&#34;&gt;biography&lt;/a&gt; which is going to be released in early 2012. This man started Apple in his parent&amp;rsquo;s garage and after several problems the company now turned into the empire. His pet projects are all at ultimate level - Macintosh, iMac, OS X, iPod, iPhone, iPad.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Zuckerberg’s Sister Randi Zuckerberg Quits Facebook [Resignation Letter]</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-08-04-mark-zuckerbergs-sister-randi-zuckerberg-quits-facebook-resignation-letter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-08-04-mark-zuckerbergs-sister-randi-zuckerberg-quits-facebook-resignation-letter/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Randi Zuckerberg is leaving Facebook to start her own social media company called &lt;strong&gt;RtoZ&lt;/strong&gt; Media. Randi is the Director of marketing has been with Facebook since near the beginning of the company’s rise to power.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She had gone on a maternity leave three months ago, and instead returning to the company , she submitted a letter of resignation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/-wcjoic0ioDo/TjpGiF4XZVI/AAAAAAAAFjc/uZL3qaykmHo/s1600-h/image%25255B6%25255D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh5.ggpht.com/-h0MUyLOewuI/TjpGlnEU-kI/AAAAAAAAFjg/ysiXuvE72Xw/image_thumb%25255B2%25255D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Her resignation letter included a summary of achievements during her 6 years journey at Facebook -&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>“It feels like editing an English paper” – 19 Year Old iPhone Hacker</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-08-01-it-feels-like-editing-an-english-paper-19-year-old-iphone-hacker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-08-01-it-feels-like-editing-an-english-paper-19-year-old-iphone-hacker/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This 19 year old chap who always keeps low profile and a prominent member of the iOS jailbreak community agreed to be interviewed by Forbes where he told about his real life and interests.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh4.ggpht.com/-EHCZlhsoRPk/Tjb3V08iamI/AAAAAAAAFiU/w5YnG6NBKa0/s1600-h/image%25255B5%25255D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh3.ggpht.com/-mFD_H5R52IQ/Tjb3YgUaXcI/AAAAAAAAFiY/oFaXmjaxhj4/image_thumb%25255B3%25255D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Until now, we have seen this Apple hacker as &lt;strong&gt;Comex&lt;/strong&gt; (@comex on Twitter) is the author of JailbreakMe, an awesome easy web only jail breaking tool for the iPhone, iPod, iPad devices. JailbreakMe, unlike other tools, doesn’t require a computer connection or major knowledge on how iOS operates since it relies on a PDF exploit found in Mobile Safari - just by pointing the browser to JailbreakMe’s website and following the easy on-screen instructions. It merely lets users install any application they want on their devices. But jail breaking, as the  practice is called, violates Apple’s obsessive control of its gadgets and demonstrates software holes that could be exploited later by less benevolent hackers.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Get Google&#43; Invite Right Now</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-07-01-how-to-get-google-invite-right-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-07-01-how-to-get-google-invite-right-now/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So, the Facebook killer is out and everybody around the globe who got invites are playing with this new awesome product from Google. If you are too late to be invited by Google, this project &lt;strong&gt;Google+&lt;/strong&gt; now stopped sending invites on its own because of huge response!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And there are people selling these invites on eBay for money too!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/-3Sgz5Cm7KAk/Tg22Qp028fI/AAAAAAAACHc/QUdJ6iotZAw/s1600-h/image%25255B2%25255D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh3.ggpht.com/-s12j_CyE_nw/Tg22SJDtzYI/AAAAAAAACHg/HijSlSp-AJY/image_thumb.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This trick takes the hidden feature of Circles service, which is a part of Google+ project. This allows you to send invites to a list of email addresses. Until Google decides to catch it and make Google+ completely live, follow these simple steps.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS 5 Beta Crashes With Headphones and Music App [Video]</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-06-28-ios-5-beta-crashes-with-headphones-and-music-app-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-06-28-ios-5-beta-crashes-with-headphones-and-music-app-video/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Apple recently announced the next iOS version, &lt;strong&gt;iOS 5&lt;/strong&gt; which includes amazing new features – notification centre, improved home screen, and much more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even though this is in beta, there is a weird bug where the OS crashes on the whole when the music app is launched with earphones or headphones plugged in. I am not sure this is only specific to 3rd generation iPod touches but the bug is still present in &lt;strong&gt;iOS 5 beta 2&lt;/strong&gt; (it is even present in Beta 1) which is released on July 24, 2011.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shopping Online: Your Guide to Buying a Laptop</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-06-24-shopping-online-your-guide-to-buying-a-laptop/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-06-24-shopping-online-your-guide-to-buying-a-laptop/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-HC4nDGxpPFo/TgSluVSElVI/AAAAAAAACG0/zLu9hqJYGJc/s1600/cool-laptop.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;//localhost:1313/posts/2011-06-24-shopping-online-your-guide-to-buying-a-laptop/images/cool-laptop.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Buying a new laptop is often confusing for many of us if we’re not tech savvy enough to understand all the jargon or just plain don’t know the requirements we are looking for. With that in mind we’ve put together a brief guide to choosing yourself a laptop which should make it easier for you to end up with the right model for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Defining your usage&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
This is the most important step in buying a laptop as many people buy laptops that either exceed or do not meet their requirements. Buying a poor quality laptop will end up costing you more in the long run and buying too high a quality laptop is simply a waste of money. So you need to determine your usage. If you mainly use your laptop for work, email etc then you can get by with a very low end computer as you don’t require a lot of memory or performance based hardware. If you want a laptop for digital design or gaming then you will need a much higher performance, a good graphics card and a lot of memory. If you use your computer as your primary media device then you will also want a good quality sound card and a high quality screen. If you determine your usage in this way you should be able to have a much better idea of what you need.&lt;br&gt;
                Secondly you need to determine how mobile you want your laptop to be. If you intend to travel with it extensively for work or require something with a long battery life for extended trips away then you need to analyse these requirements. Generally this information will be clear but always minus a few hours from the battery life as this tends to be a best case figure. Sacrificing size for battery life or vice versa is worth considering depending on your needs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaked Pictures of Nokia’s First Windows Phone. Codenamed ‘SeaRay’</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-06-23-leaked-pictures-of-nokias-first-windows-phone-codenamed-searay/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-06-23-leaked-pictures-of-nokias-first-windows-phone-codenamed-searay/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ok. This one is a big leak! Earlier today, pictures and video of Nokia’s first man, CEO &lt;strong&gt;Stephen Elop&lt;/strong&gt; announcing first Windows Phone to the company’s employees surfaced the blogosphere.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/-FNy2F1pom2M/TgNXN6lfcLI/AAAAAAAACGc/857UDFSPdtY/s1600-h/image%25255B2%25255D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/image%25255B5%25255D.png&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/image%25255B8%25255D.png&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/-1PpVG4I7IWI/TgNXSE3mfRI/AAAAAAAACGw/S47vlF_pIrA/image_thumb%25255B2%25255D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And here is the important part of the video -&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.technet.hu/telefon/20110624/exkluziv_video_elop_bemutatja_az_elso_windowsos_nokiat/&#34;&gt;Thanks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>cosmoGeek Turns ONE, Keeps on Growing</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-06-17-cosmogeek-turns-one-keeps-on-growing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-06-17-cosmogeek-turns-one-keeps-on-growing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wow! I can’t believe you’re ONE already!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/-fiUJqwgKEds/TftrKeV1KOI/AAAAAAAACF0/v-rTENHZSpY/s1600-h/image%25255B2%25255D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/-cC0cmlfTpAQ/TftrLglA5vI/AAAAAAAACF4/dOsjSR8p4SI/image_thumb.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Its officially the one year birthday of &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmoGeek.info&#34;&gt;www.cosmoGeek.info&lt;/a&gt; and I can’t tell you how excited I am to have made it this far. I’ve loved every minute of this tech blogging covering the most excited happening around Microsoft, Google, Apple, Facebook, Twitter, and so on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With &lt;strong&gt;19,282 Pageviews&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;11,605 visits&lt;/strong&gt;, and more than &lt;strong&gt;290 posts&lt;/strong&gt; – this one year, I’ve enjoyed the support of every tech blogger around the globe.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Stream Your Music Library using Google Music</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-06-17-how-to-stream-your-music-library-using-google-music/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-06-17-how-to-stream-your-music-library-using-google-music/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Having to sync all your music between devices is a bit annoying stuff. Few days ago, Google &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/2011/05/google-io-2011-day-1-highlights-android_15.html&#34;&gt;launched&lt;/a&gt; a new music service &lt;strong&gt;Google Music&lt;/strong&gt; that lets you upload your personal music collection to the cloud from which you can play them from anywhere directly on computer and Android devices.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This service is now in beta mode and invitation based for the United States users only. I managed to get the invitation yesterday night and uploaded around 330 songs from my library. This article gives a sneak peak of this next generation cloud service.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gevey SIM – The Only Working Method to Unlock Any iPhone 4</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-06-11-gevey-sim-the-only-working-method-to-unlock-any-iphone-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-06-11-gevey-sim-the-only-working-method-to-unlock-any-iphone-4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh4.ggpht.com/-6M_BNjgOrOA/TfPV-6-dXHI/AAAAAAAACEQ/ihTw1rKg404/s1600-h/image%25255B8%25255D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh5.ggpht.com/-CtQyfxiCM-o/TfPWBNA9jCI/AAAAAAAACEU/YKy1vs4R4as/image_thumb%25255B4%25255D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Are you one of the users who tired of waiting &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/2011/03/bad-news-about-iphone-4-unlock.html&#34;&gt;software based unlock&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; to unlock your iPhone 4 ? You may already heard of this hardware based unlock method – &lt;strong&gt;Gevey SIM Interposer,&lt;/strong&gt; a Turbo SIM like piggy back sim card that allows you to unlock any iPhone 4 (all basebands up to &lt;strong&gt;04.11.04&lt;/strong&gt; including &lt;strong&gt;iOS 5 beta&lt;/strong&gt;) and does not even require to jailbreak your device.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This method is still questionable in terms of its legal issues and readers are encouraged to try at their own risk.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Today is Geek Pride Day! List of Rights and Responsibilities</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-05-25-today-is-geek-pride-day-list-of-rights-and-responsibilities/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-05-25-today-is-geek-pride-day-list-of-rights-and-responsibilities/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Do you know what today is? Its Geek Pride Day! Yay!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today was declared &lt;strong&gt;Geek Pride Day&lt;/strong&gt; to commemorate the release of the first &lt;strong&gt;Star Wars&lt;/strong&gt; film on May 25th, 1977.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But according to Wikipedia, this day wasn’t officially acknowledged until 2008/2009 when it started to grow mass appeal and grabbed the attention of bloggers locally in New York, others around the world, and then eventually the main stream media.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 Best Android 2.2 Phones below Rs. 10,000 in India</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-05-23-5-best-android-2-2-phones-below-rs-10000-in-india/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-05-23-5-best-android-2-2-phones-below-rs-10000-in-india/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I remember many guys asking me for an Android handset within a budget of &lt;strong&gt;Rs. 10,000&lt;/strong&gt;. Why Android created this fuss? Yes, its &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/2011/05/google-io-2011-day-1-highlights-android_15.html&#34;&gt;Android everywhere!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When comes to Indian market, Nokia still retains 60% of market share, while Android started creating buzz. If you are searching for good cheap Android handset in India with a budget below Rs. 10,000, then this post might be useful to you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The prices mentioned below are taken from &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.flipkart.com/&#34;&gt;Flipcart&lt;/a&gt; and it may be slightly high or less in your region. All devices are in &lt;strong&gt;Android 2.2&lt;/strong&gt; club.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Google Chromebooks Is An Ideal Solution for Organizations?</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-05-14-why-google-chromebooks-is-an-ideal-solution-for-organizations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-05-14-why-google-chromebooks-is-an-ideal-solution-for-organizations/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Even with dedicated IT departments, businesses and schools struggle with the complex, costly, insecure computers. Staging, imaging, updating and repairing software problems are some of the daily activities - a typical IT department is responsible for.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Crashes, long boot times, application conflicts, endless updates, viruses, security issues and obsolete hardware all frustrate IT managers and end users - and most users don’t need or want the complexity and annoyance of their current PCs.&lt;br&gt;
On the second day of Google I/O 2011 event, May 11, Sundar Pichai, senior vice president of Chrome, announced the first set &lt;strong&gt;Chromebooks&lt;/strong&gt;. These are not typical notebooks.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developers, Developers, Developers By Steve Ballmer</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-05-05-developers-developers-developers-by-steve-ballmer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-05-05-developers-developers-developers-by-steve-ballmer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Do you remember Steve Ballmer toning ‘&lt;strong&gt;Developers, Developers, Developers…’&lt;/strong&gt; which had set the Internet surprise! Ballmer is quite passionate about technology and of course Developers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh4.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TcLHRlD3vzI/AAAAAAAAB9s/xAb2uetsoa8/s1600-h/image%5B4%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TcLHSgdFcpI/AAAAAAAAB9w/RsbI0zdoqEY/image_thumb%5B2%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is the original version of that video taken from YouTube -&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Surprised? Now, this original video was &lt;strong&gt;remixed&lt;/strong&gt; with fabulous lyrics. Listen now!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a must hear for every developer and check out the &lt;strong&gt;lyrics&lt;/strong&gt; -&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I’m a developer&lt;br&gt;
in many senses of the word&lt;br&gt;
cause I make these applications&lt;br&gt;
but I also use these verbs&lt;br&gt;
to make this music&lt;br&gt;
I construct it line by line&lt;br&gt;
just like when I’m coding&lt;br&gt;
another software design&lt;br&gt;
in both cases&lt;br&gt;
its about design patterns&lt;br&gt;
anyone can get the job done&lt;br&gt;
its the execution that matters&lt;br&gt;
I have many interests&lt;br&gt;
sometimes they conflict&lt;br&gt;
my creativity can usually be a benefit&lt;br&gt;
but sometimes it keeps me&lt;br&gt;
far too busy&lt;br&gt;
but I can’t complain&lt;br&gt;
because my life is hardly gritty&lt;br&gt;
so I think i’ll sit back&lt;br&gt;
and pen myself another ditty&lt;br&gt;
why is it that Linus Torvalds&lt;br&gt;
the only one that Gits me&lt;br&gt;
did you get that reference I was using&lt;br&gt;
or is the thought of source source control too confusing&lt;br&gt;
may just lay myself down a Team Foundation&lt;br&gt;
so I can test the objects of my creation&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do you suffer from Facebook Addiction Disorder?</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-04-30-do-you-suffer-from-facebook-addiction-disorder/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-04-30-do-you-suffer-from-facebook-addiction-disorder/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Many netizens are finding it harder and harder to stay away from social networking sites and experts have figures like around 350 million users suffer from &lt;strong&gt;Facebook Addiction Disorder (FAD).&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You won’t find FAD in any medical text book but this is true. More than half of Facebook’s total membership log on at least once in a day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You might be thinking that I don’t have FAD and this is all rubbish. “&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.allfacebook.com/do-you-suffer-from-facebook-addiction-disorder-2011-04&#34;&gt;AllFacebook&lt;/a&gt;” posted an interesting set of questions to examine whether you are &lt;strong&gt;Facebookaholic&lt;/strong&gt; -&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Amazon yesterday?</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-04-22-what-happened-to-amazon-yesterday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-04-22-what-happened-to-amazon-yesterday/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Yesterday was an interesting day for many (I mean many) sites around the world which rely on &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/2010/10/amazon-web-services-aws-offers-free.html&#34;&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; servers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Amazon EC2 (Elastic Compute Cloud),&lt;/strong&gt; an amazing implementation of Cloud Computing had a major network failure yesterday that triggered a re-mirror of all the &lt;strong&gt;Elastic Block Storage (EBS)&lt;/strong&gt; volumes in the North Virginia data centre.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This re-mirror combined with a large number of customers trying to fire up new instances to recover from the network failure caused Amazon to hit a storage capacity problem.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your iPhone Secretly Records Your Location</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-04-21-your-iphone-secretly-records-your-location/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-04-21-your-iphone-secretly-records-your-location/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We are know that iPhone can track user location. But, how many of knew that the iPhone &lt;strong&gt;constantly tracks your location and records your coordinates&lt;/strong&gt; alongside a time stamp to a secret file?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This secret file is also copied to owner’s computer when the two are synchronised.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh4.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TbAuva12ijI/AAAAAAAAB7o/vmR5OptojiU/s1600-h/image%5B3%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/image%5B8%5D.png&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh5.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TbAuyR-3KuI/AAAAAAAAB70/HW1PgRhxz-4/image_thumb%5B4%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s so bad about this?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The most immediate problem is that this data is stored in an easily-readable form on your machine. Any other program you run or user with access to your machine can look through it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Unlock iPhone 4, 3GS with iOS 4.3.1</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-04-10-how-to-unlock-iphone-4-3gs-with-ios-4-3-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-04-10-how-to-unlock-iphone-4-3gs-with-ios-4-3-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As expected earlier &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/#!/k_avinash/status/56836221271412736&#34;&gt;today&lt;/a&gt;, the Dev team released an unlock for &lt;strong&gt;iPhone 4, 3GS&lt;/strong&gt; devices running &lt;strong&gt;01.59.00, 04.26.08, 05.11.07, 05.12.01, 05.13.04, and 06.15.00&lt;/strong&gt; basebands.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If your baseband is different from any of these, there is no unlock available at this time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Its already &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/2011/01/no-more-ios-updates-unlocks-jailbreaks.html&#34;&gt;confirmed&lt;/a&gt; in the past that there will be no iOS updates, unlocks, jailbreaks for iPhone 3G and iPod touch 2G models.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TaF-OnyiCgI/AAAAAAAAB6s/zw4Abx_nQ1k/s1600-h/image%5B3%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TaF-SuiupcI/AAAAAAAAB6w/J1wx4mO122U/image_thumb%5B1%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tutorial for iPhone 4 Windows users only:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Facebook Spam – America’s Got Talent Lady Video</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-04-09-new-facebook-spam-americas-got-talent-lady-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-04-09-new-facebook-spam-americas-got-talent-lady-video/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A new kind of ‘Click-Jacking’ and ‘Like-Jacking’ is spreading on Facebook. This time with a whole index of suggestive, funny and controversial videos.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have seen similar kind of Facebook &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/2011/02/fb-spam-i-was-logged-into-facebook-for.html&#34;&gt;spams&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/2011/03/hoax-facebook-will-not-use-your-photos.html&#34;&gt;hoaxes&lt;/a&gt; in the past and &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/k_avinash&#34;&gt;cosmoGeek&lt;/a&gt; instantly alerted its readers &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/2010/12/how-to-get-rid-of-facebook-360-images.html&#34;&gt;how to&lt;/a&gt; get rid from these kind of accidental clicks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh3.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TaDkgsGYCJI/AAAAAAAAB6c/42hcoxNQNqk/s1600-h/image%5B13%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/image%5B12%5D.png&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh4.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TaDkk_20JjI/AAAAAAAAB6o/2nVUbVWdZD4/image_thumb%5B6%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A Lady smashed big cans of bear with her BIG BOOBS on America&amp;rsquo;s Got Talent, Checkout now!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once you click on the wall post link, you will be taken to a page displayed with a video link. Clicking play will hijack your account and you will be spreading the spam via your news feed.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All Google’s April Fools Jokes [2000-2011]</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-04-01-all-googles-april-fools-jokes-2000-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-04-01-all-googles-april-fools-jokes-2000-2011/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/search/label/Google&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Google&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; has a tradition of perpetrating April Fools’ Day hoaxes. Since 2000, Google has published one or more chokes each year (except 2001 and 2003), sometimes around 17 chokes a year.&lt;br&gt;
Many of them were a huge hit and funny!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh3.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TZXp7JT5dJI/AAAAAAAAB5w/rCKyeOsU2M8/s1600-h/image%5B3%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/image%5B7%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/image%5B12%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh5.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TZXp_-l0PoI/AAAAAAAAB6E/orv7LqR8IAk/image_thumb%5B6%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[via] Wikipedia&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hoax! Facebook Will Not Use Your Photos In Ads</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-03-19-hoax-facebook-will-not-use-your-photos-in-ads/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-03-19-hoax-facebook-will-not-use-your-photos-in-ads/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This rumor about Facebook using your photos in ads without your consent is spreading again. The rumor was not true earlier (back in 2009) and it is not true now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many Facebook users are saying in a status message that’s being passed and worried that Facebook plans to use their photos in Facebook ads, and they&amp;rsquo;re telling everyone to change privacy settings to prevent it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh3.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TYSJTwHXguI/AAAAAAAAB38/A4rngMI2wwg/s1600-h/image%5B3%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/image%5B7%5D.png&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TYSJZZ-sEjI/AAAAAAAAB4I/gumCmoWF0Lw/image_thumb%5B3%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&#34;_on-friday-facebook-will-start-using-your-photos-in-ads-that-appear-on-the-profile-page-of-your-friends-its-legal-and-mentioned-in-the-fine-print-when-you-create-your-account-to-stop-this-do-the-following-got-to-account-account-settings-click-on-facebook-ads-choose-no-one-in-both-drop-down-menus-scroll-down-for-2nd-and-save-changes-for-each-drop-down-please-copy-this-and-use-in-a-status-update_&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;On Friday, Facebook will start using your photos in ads that appear on the profile page of your friends. It&amp;rsquo;s legal and mentioned in the fine print when you create your account. To STOP this do the following: got to Account, Account Settings, click on Facebook Ads, choose &amp;ldquo;No one&amp;rdquo; in BOTH drop-down menus (scroll down for 2nd) and save changes for EACH drop-down. Please copy this and use in a status update.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let me start off by saying this rumor is &lt;strong&gt;FALSE&lt;/strong&gt;. Facebook has also &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.facebook.com/blog.php?post=110636457130&#34;&gt;confirmed&lt;/a&gt; it is false. It was initially started back in July 2009, and has more recently shot up again.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Removed 21 Malware Apps. Remotely Removing from Affected Android Devices</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-03-07-google-removed-21-malware-apps-remotely-removing-from-affected-android-devices/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-03-07-google-removed-21-malware-apps-remotely-removing-from-affected-android-devices/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last week, the Android team was made aware of a number of malicious applications published to Android Market. Within minutes of becoming aware, they removed the malicious applications. According to the company, the apps are malware aimed at getting root access to the user’s device, gathering a wide range of available data, and downloading more code to it without the user’s knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh4.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TXT4ZQv-dZI/AAAAAAAAB3A/12Lk4CrUXwM/s1600-h/image%5B7%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh3.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TXT4apHYlyI/AAAAAAAAB3E/58QfkYcgT8Q/image_thumb%5B3%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The following 21 malware apps have already been downloaded by at least 50, 000 Android users.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple Announces iPad 2 – Thinner. Lighter. Faster.</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-03-02-apple-announces-ipad-2-thinner-lighter-faster/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-03-02-apple-announces-ipad-2-thinner-lighter-faster/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The wait is over. Apple CEO Steve Jobs, who is taking a leave absence from the company, returned to unveil the new product &lt;strong&gt;iPad 2&lt;/strong&gt; at the Yerba Buena Center in San Francisco today. As rumored, the next generation tablet device will have a 33% thinner profile.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh3.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TW6fQVwb4II/AAAAAAAAB1k/vM2BEJUtws8/s1600-h/image%5B4%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/image%5B10%5D.png&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/image%5B23%5D.png&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/image%5B15%5D.png&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh3.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TW6fdGIEE5I/AAAAAAAAB2A/BxR6VQZV61k/image_thumb%5B9%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Other awesome features you can play on this new iPad 2 include&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Photo Booth  -&lt;/strong&gt; you can manipulate effects by touching.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can &lt;strong&gt;FaceTime&lt;/strong&gt; between two iPads, between an iPad and an iPhone, or between an iPad and a Mac.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Young Bill Gates and Steve Jobs</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-02-26-young-bill-gates-and-steve-jobs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-02-26-young-bill-gates-and-steve-jobs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Nothing special about this post. Just sharing a classic picture of the legends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh3.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TWlz3jrTBDI/AAAAAAAAB0g/Ojqh6w91rjc/s1600-h/Yyoung%20Bill%20Gates%20and%20Steve%20Jobs%5B5%5D.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Yyoung Bill Gates and Steve Jobs&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh3.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TWlz4vRXV1I/AAAAAAAAB0k/dwwMTZi3Kp0/Yyoung%20Bill%20Gates%20and%20Steve%20Jobs_thumb%5B2%5D.jpg?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;Yyoung Bill Gates and Steve Jobs&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A short description from Wikipedia:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steven Paul Jobs&lt;/strong&gt; (born February 24, 1955) is an American business magnate and inventor. He is the co-founder and chief executive officer of &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/search/label/Apple&#34;&gt;Apple Inc&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. Jobs also previously served as chief executive of Pixar Animation Studios; he became a member of the board of The Walt Disney Company in 2006, following the acquisition of Pixar by Disney. He was credited in the 1995 movie Toy Story as an executive producer.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>“Google Recipe” Now Teaches You Cooking!</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-02-25-google-recipe-now-teaches-you-cooking/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-02-25-google-recipe-now-teaches-you-cooking/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As a computer geek, I prefer to work with complex gadgets and problems, but when somebody talks about ‘cooking’ which I never tried till now – thanks to &lt;strong&gt;Google Recipe&lt;/strong&gt; – the new tool which teaches your cooking in a smart way!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.google.com/landing/recipes/&#34;&gt;Recipe View&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; lets you narrow your search results to show only recipes, and helps you choose the right recipe amongst the search results by showing clearly marked ratings, ingredients and pictures.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google: Microsoft Is Cheating and Copying Our Search Results</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-02-02-google-microsoft-is-cheating-and-copying-our-search-results/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-02-02-google-microsoft-is-cheating-and-copying-our-search-results/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Google set up a sting operation (!) in an attempt to catch Microsoft red-handed stealing their search results in Bing. Interestingly, Bing doesn’t deny this completely.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The whole sting operation is amazing and it started from Danny Sullivan’s &lt;a href=&#34;http://searchengineland.com/google-bing-is-cheating-copying-our-search-results-62914&#34;&gt;post&lt;/a&gt; and resulting Microsoft’s response on Bing search &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.bing.com/community/site_blogs/b/search/archive/2011/02/01/thoughts-on-search-quality.aspx&#34;&gt;quality&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh3.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TUkD5LDdORI/AAAAAAAABvc/Oyzca0miUNQ/s1600-h/image%5B3%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/image%5B8%5D.png&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/image%5B15%5D.png&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TUkD9sQSK3I/AAAAAAAABvw/4Pe7yjepvsc/image_thumb%5B9%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;uld ever enter into Google.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These searches returned no matches on Google or Bing — or a tiny number of poor quality matches, in a few cases — before the experiment went live. With the code enabled, Google placed a honeypot page to show up at the top of each synthetic search.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Print From Anywhere Using Google Cloud Print</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-01-25-print-from-anywhere-using-google-cloud-print/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-01-25-print-from-anywhere-using-google-cloud-print/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The future looks great on paper! Cloud is now becoming reality. You can now print from anywhere using Google Cloud Print.&lt;br&gt;
Google blew the lid off of Chrome OS by introducing Google Cloud Print Beta. Google Cloud Print makes printing more intuitive, accessible and useful, by allowing you to print to your printers from Google Cloud Print enabled apps on any computer or smart phone.&lt;br&gt;
By connecting your printer with the Google Cloud you will be able to print to your printer from any computer or smart phone, regardless of where you are. Just activate the Google Cloud Print connector in Google Chrome and your printer will automatically be available to you from Google Cloud Print enabled web and mobile apps.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is the iPod Really That Much Greater than a Regular MP3 Player?</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-01-10-is-the-ipod-really-that-much-greater-than-a-regular-mp3-player/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2011-01-10-is-the-ipod-really-that-much-greater-than-a-regular-mp3-player/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It might sound like blasphemy for the Apple diehards out there, but in the world of MP3 players, the ability to play a lot of songs isn’t that innovative of a feature anymore. The original iPod, of course, advertised itself as allowing you to put a thousand songs in your pocket -  but this original (albeit compelling) sales pitch seems to have lost its luster as the technology has caught up with the times.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 50 Passwords You Should Never Use</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-12-15-top-50-passwords-you-should-never-use/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-12-15-top-50-passwords-you-should-never-use/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Are you one of the many people who is using a dangerously easy-to-guess password? Change your password before its too late!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Twitter, LinkedIn, World of Warcraft and Yahoo are amongst the popular websites which are advising users to change their passwords in light of the &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/2010/12/linkedin-suspended-gawker-hacked-user.html&#34;&gt;recent security breach&lt;/a&gt; at the Gawker Media family of sites.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh4.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TQjWLixRbiI/AAAAAAAABnQ/HkiU5MLP1q4/s1600-h/image%5B3%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/image%5B11%5D.png&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh3.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TQjWOkn8VMI/AAAAAAAABnc/cttBhrb6vx4/image_thumb%5B7%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Clearly people need to get out of the habit of using the same password everywhere, and they also need to ensure that their passwords are not easy to guess or crack. Why don&amp;rsquo;t more websites test the password that you&amp;rsquo;ve chosen to ensure that it&amp;rsquo;s strong enough and reject?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>cosmoGeek Featured On Alltop.com</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-12-14-cosmogeek-featured-on-alltop-com/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-12-14-cosmogeek-featured-on-alltop-com/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m really glad to announce that &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info&#34;&gt;cosmoGeek&lt;/a&gt; is now featured on Alltop.com, a popular news aggregating site. Alltop is an “online magazine rack” of the web.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info&#34;&gt;cosmoGeek&lt;/a&gt; will be sharing the space in the top technology &lt;a href=&#34;http://tech.alltop.com/&#34;&gt;news page&lt;/a&gt; along with some high profile blogs like Mashable, Techcrunch, Engadget and many more!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh5.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TQdUS5vuAoI/AAAAAAAABl4/4Dxki4UjagQ/s1600-h/image%5B3%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/image%5B10%5D.png&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh3.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TQdUVrFR_rI/AAAAAAAABmE/nExBGXFR5II/image_thumb%5B6%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happy 25th Birthday Windows!</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-11-20-happy-25th-birthday-windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-11-20-happy-25th-birthday-windows/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Microsoft Windows completes 25 years today. &lt;strong&gt;On November 20, 1985&lt;/strong&gt;, the first version &lt;strong&gt;Windows 1.0&lt;/strong&gt; was released.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Can you recall how Windows 1.0 looked like? To be frank, I was born in the same year and no real hands-on experience for me until Windows 95! .&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh4.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TOf10DcsMcI/AAAAAAAABiE/-NAaCRqmumE/s1600-h/image%5B3%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/image%5B8%5D.png&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/image%5B12%5D.png&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/image%5B16%5D.png&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/image%5B20%5D.png&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/image%5B24%5D.png&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/image%5B28%5D.png&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/image%5B32%5D.png&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/image%5B36%5D.png&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/image%5B40%5D.png&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/image%5B45%5D.png&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/image%5B49%5D.png&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/image%5B53%5D.png&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh4.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TOf2erpuYCI/AAAAAAAABjs/BqTYOYXdT4c/image_thumb%5B27%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh, and of course &lt;strong&gt;Windows 8.&lt;/strong&gt; I hardly know much about it at the moment except the &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/2010/06/windows-8-plans-leaked-many-details.html&#34;&gt;leaked&lt;/a&gt; slides. Let’s hope it is as well received as Windows 7 has been so far. &lt;strong&gt;Happy Birthday Windows!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>“Facebook Messaging” - The Next Generation Email System and Email Killer</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-11-15-facebook-messaging-the-next-generation-email-system-and-email-killer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-11-15-facebook-messaging-the-next-generation-email-system-and-email-killer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is not an “&lt;strong&gt;Email Killer&lt;/strong&gt;” – Mark Zuckerberg emphasized at the Massive Messaging Facebook event, which is happening now. Today, Facebook announced the next evolution of messaging system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh4.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TOGFkhfse8I/AAAAAAAABhg/NhAb1bqKnM8/s1600-h/image%5B9%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/image%5B10%5D.png&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/image%5B16%5D.png&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh3.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TOGFu0rWxqI/AAAAAAAABh0/P28pEWksJOE/image_thumb%5B10%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Facebook is going to launch this revolutionary messaging and email addresses gradually in next few months. Once you receive an invitation, you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to get started and also invite your friends to join you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, do you think this is a &lt;strong&gt;“Gmail Killer”&lt;/strong&gt;?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Search Your Favourite App across all Platforms at one place</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-11-03-search-your-favourite-app-across-all-platforms-at-one-place/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-11-03-search-your-favourite-app-across-all-platforms-at-one-place/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Are you an owner of a smartphone? Are you frustrated with trying the right Mobile App for your device? Do you develop Apps and want to know the contenders of your idea?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Discover the world of Mobile using &lt;strong&gt;Mimvi&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh3.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TNGb90zehTI/AAAAAAAABgA/5xjMgvSkFkA/s1600-h/image%5B3%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh5.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TNGb_AP3gsI/AAAAAAAABgE/X3s5rtNasas/image_thumb%5B1%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.mimvi.com/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mimvi&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; enables you to quickly discover Mobile Apps, Mobile Content and Mobile Products across all devices and platforms, including - Apple&amp;rsquo;s &lt;strong&gt;iPhone&lt;/strong&gt;, Google &lt;strong&gt;Android&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Blackberry&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Windows&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Nokia&lt;/strong&gt; devices – all at one single place!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Test a Website On Different Screen Sizes, Platforms and Browsers</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-10-30-how-to-test-a-website-on-different-screen-sizes-platforms-and-browsers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-10-30-how-to-test-a-website-on-different-screen-sizes-platforms-and-browsers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The first part of this tutorial explains how to test a website at the screen size of different devices like iPhone, iPad, Tablets, Android phones etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Different mobile devices have different resolutions for their screen – for example, &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/search/label/Apple&#34;&gt;Apple&lt;/a&gt; iPad has 768 x 1024 or 1024 x 768px screen size in different mode and &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/search/label/Google&#34;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; Nexus One has 480 x 800 screen pixel size. Now, if you want to see your website on these screen sizes, here is a website to resize any browser to some preset value at single click.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ballmer: Windows 8 Will Be The Riskiest Product Bet [Video]</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-10-24-ballmer-windows-8-will-be-the-riskiest-product-bet-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-10-24-ballmer-windows-8-will-be-the-riskiest-product-bet-video/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Windows 7&lt;/strong&gt; has been a powerful success for Microsoft. As an evolutionary upgrade to Vista, it patched almost all of Vista’s glaring holes: broken driver support, sluggish performance and the horribly annoying User-Account Control. It sold more than 240 million licenses in one year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Asked about the riskiest product bet the Redmond crew is currently developing, the answer is not Windows Phone 7 or Bing or even Office Web Apps - its fearless leader &lt;strong&gt;Steve Ballmer&lt;/strong&gt; took no time in answering &lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;the next release of Windows.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook introduced new version of Groups and two more new features.</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-10-07-facebook-introduced-new-version-of-groups-and-two-more-new-features/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-10-07-facebook-introduced-new-version-of-groups-and-two-more-new-features/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last night, I’ve covered live updates of Facebook event in cosmoGeek’s Facebook &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.facebook.com/cosmoGeek&#34;&gt;fan page&lt;/a&gt; and as well as on my &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/k_avinash&#34;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; account.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To summarize, Facebook yesterday revealed 3 new features - a new version of Groups, an option to download &lt;em&gt;your&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;information&lt;/em&gt; locally, new dashboard for apps you use.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1.   New Facebook Groups&lt;/strong&gt; Until now, Facebook has made it easy to share with all of your friends or with everyone, but there hasn&amp;rsquo;t been a simple way to create and maintain a space for sharing with the small communities of people in your life, like your roommates, classmates, co-workers and family&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From &#39;Pretty&#39; to &#39;Professional&#39;</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-09-12-from-pretty-to-professional/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-09-12-from-pretty-to-professional/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;On the occasion of cosmoGeek&amp;rsquo;s 180 days completion, I am proud to announce its brand new so called &lt;strong&gt;&amp;lsquo;Professional&amp;rsquo;&lt;/strong&gt; look today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exclusive features of this new theme -&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Top link bar – Posts are now broadly categorized&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fast Page load&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Brand new custom &amp;lsquo;cosmoGeek’ Logo&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;JScript ‘Slider’ with featured posts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New social plugins&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Facebook &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.facebook.com/cosmoGeek?v=app_112078882147346&amp;amp;ref=sgm&#34;&gt;Fan Page&lt;/a&gt; got a new Welcome page&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh3.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TI0XehmzMUI/AAAAAAAABXM/NU2Cl7kt4Ig/s1600-h/image%5B6%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh5.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TI0XhP7zhOI/AAAAAAAABXQ/upLW6BiHHBY/image_thumb%5B4%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More features to come -&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Breadcrumb&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Related posts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Google custom search box&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Social ‘Share’ buttons&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Twitter feed box&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Facebook comments box&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is a lot of hard work behind this new look and suggestions are most welcome.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shocker! Android Logo Has Been Stolen from Atari Game “Gauntlet”</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-09-03-shocker-android-logo-has-been-stolen-from-atari-game-gauntlet/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-09-03-shocker-android-logo-has-been-stolen-from-atari-game-gauntlet/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The discovery of a similar looking character in an arcade-style action game of 90s by Atari titled, &lt;strong&gt;Gauntlet: The Third Encounter&lt;/strong&gt; has caused much stir in the blogosphere today. Google’s Android logo has turned out to be a look alike of one of the characters of the game. Surprisingly, even the name of the character (“&lt;strong&gt;Android&lt;/strong&gt;”) is same, among others namely Wizard, Valkyrie, Samurai, Gunfighter, Pirate, Punk Rocker, and Nerd. Developed and published by Atari Games in the 1990 for the Atari Lynx, Gauntlet is considered as one of the most popular multiplayer arcade role-playing game of that time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happy Sys Admin Appreciation Day!</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-07-30-happy-sys-admin-appreciation-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-07-30-happy-sys-admin-appreciation-day/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Friday, July 30, 2010 (Last Friday of July) is the System Administrator Appreciation Day.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes, today marks the 11th annual celebration of systems administrators everywhere. It’s a day when you should stop and appreciate the people that keep those servers running and those backups fresh, not shake your fist at them for your poor 99.9% uptime.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh4.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TFMISe0bm4I/AAAAAAAABSU/yqhYsF44sWA/s1600-h/image%5B3%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TFMIT_t3y2I/AAAAAAAABSY/FkOCnBXa9bw/image_thumb%5B1%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On this special day, I would like to advice to employees on the proper use of the System Administrator’s valuable time!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple admits iPhone 4 Reception Problems as ‘Incorrect Signal Display’</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-07-02-apple-admits-iphone-4-reception-problems-as-incorrect-signal-display/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-07-02-apple-admits-iphone-4-reception-problems-as-incorrect-signal-display/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;According to a press release issued by the company, Apple admits iPhone 4 reception problems as ‘Incorrect Signal Display’. The iPhone 4 doesn’t have a hardware design flaw – it has a software bug.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;We were stunned to find that the formula we use to calculate how many bars of signal strength to display is totally wrong,&amp;rdquo; says Apple. &amp;ldquo;Our formula, in many instances, mistakenly displays 2 more bars than it should for a given signal strength.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Link to &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.apple.com/pr/library/2010/07/02appleletter.html&#34;&gt;Full Announcement&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
They promise their software update will fix the way the iPhone 4 displays signal bars. However, they don&amp;rsquo;t claim the software patch would solve the signal attenuation problem caused by holding the iPhone 4 and touching the dead spot on its left bottom corner. The software patch will show the drop more accurately in the signal bar display.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 8 Plans Leaked: Many Details Revealed</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-06-29-windows-8-plans-leaked-many-details-revealed/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-06-29-windows-8-plans-leaked-many-details-revealed/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Italian Windows site “Windowsette” got a hold of some super secret squirrel Microsoft presentations laying around on the Internet somewhere. The original leak comes from the Microsoft Journal, an enthusiast blog written by Francisco Martin, who lists himself as a Microsoft VIP Tester.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Key points from the presentation:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Facial recognition:&lt;/strong&gt; A Windows computer will know who is using it based on facial recognition technology.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fast start time:&lt;/strong&gt; One of the great things about smartphones and the iPad is that it&amp;rsquo;s always on an ready to go. Laptops are increasingly speedy, but they don&amp;rsquo;t compare to mobile gadgets. Microsoft wants Windows 8 devices to be fast to start.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What are Hash Tags (#) in Twitter?</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-06-28-what-are-hash-tags-in-twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-06-28-what-are-hash-tags-in-twitter/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;What is this – &lt;strong&gt;“#”&lt;/strong&gt; sign doing in a lot of Twitter tweets? Why do most of the webmaster and bloggers use this hash symbol in their tweets?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In simple little words – it’s just categorizing or grouping your tweets like you categorize/group your blog posts in categories.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is how Twitter defines it -&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;Because Twitter provided no easy way to group tweets or add extra data, the Twitter community came up with their own way: hashtags. A hashtag is similar to other web tags it helps add tweets to a category. Hashtags have the ‘hash’ or ‘pound’ symbol (#) preceding the tag, like so: #traffic, #followfriday, #hashtag.”&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Custom Domain (www.cosmoGeek.info) graduates now!</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-06-27-my-custom-domain-www-cosmogeek-info-graduates-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-06-27-my-custom-domain-www-cosmogeek-info-graduates-now/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s going to be one of those crazy-busy-full-of-wonderful months, I predict. ;) I&amp;rsquo;m so excited to share with you some new features to my blog (&lt;a href=&#34;http://avinashkblog.blogspot.com&#34;&gt;http://avinashkblog.blogspot.com)&lt;/a&gt;). This blog is at its peak in just 100 days and its an honor and I am so excited to put even more effort and love into this blog. Most of you know that I have purchased a custom domain last week and now I am so excited to graduate it to public - &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://cosmogeek.info/&#34;&gt;www.cosmoGeek.info&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1342 page views – 43 posts – $16.68 in 60 days– ThanQ All!</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-05-16-1342-page-views-43-posts-16-68-in-60-days-thanq-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-05-16-1342-page-views-43-posts-16-68-in-60-days-thanq-all/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In its 60days of launch, this blog is currently at its peak level with 43 posts (&lt;em&gt;not many though)&lt;/em&gt; and 1342 page views altogether!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is the detailed report:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Visits overview:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh4.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/S-76E6AOSMI/AAAAAAAABMw/oixP0gEKAR8/s1600-h/image%5B30%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/image%5B31%5D.png&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/image%5B32%5D.png&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/image%5B33%5D.png&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/S-76NDWXGiI/AAAAAAAABNM/RDBM_AXIzyQ/image_thumb%5B23%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I would discuss AdSense reports on some other day. Thank you all!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to use Office 2010 RTM Free for 6 Months</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-05-14-how-to-use-office-2010-rtm-free-for-6-months/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-05-14-how-to-use-office-2010-rtm-free-for-6-months/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Now that Microsoft has released Office 2010 Final build officially to public, you can download the 60-day trial version from the link &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.microsoft.com/office/2010/en/download-office-professional-plus/default.aspx&#34; title=&#34;http://www.microsoft.com/office/2010/en/download-office-professional-plus/default.aspx&#34;&gt;http://www.microsoft.com/office/2010/en/download-office-professional-plus/default.aspx&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After installing it, user will have initial 30 days of free evaluation period before having to activate the product for lifetime continuous usage. Now to extend this expiry period to 6 months, we have to &lt;strong&gt;REARM&lt;/strong&gt; the product. &lt;em&gt;(Just follow the steps below instead of searching for REARM!)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 11 Companies That Tried To Buy Facebook</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-05-14-the-11-companies-that-tried-to-buy-facebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-05-14-the-11-companies-that-tried-to-buy-facebook/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Facebook isn&amp;rsquo;t just popular with its 500 million or so users.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to the copy of &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.amazon.com/Facebook-Effect-Inside-Company-Connecting/dp/1439102112/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;s=books&amp;amp;qid=1260660620&amp;amp;sr=1-1&#34;&gt;The Facebook Effect&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;/strong&gt; Fortune editor David Kirkpatrick&amp;rsquo;s brilliantly-reported new book about the company&amp;rsquo;s founding, Facebook has also always been very popular with the M&amp;amp;A suits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Below is the list of all the companies that swung and missed&amp;ndash;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;1. In June 2004, an unnamed financier offered $10 million&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;2. Friendster also tried to buy Facebook&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We Love Apple - Adobe</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-05-13-we-love-apple-adobe/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-05-13-we-love-apple-adobe/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Adobe is thinking different countering Apple’s hate with love.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This blog readers already knew that Steve Jobs announced in the past of removing Flash support from Apple products -&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://avinashkblog.blogspot.com/2010/05/we-are-removing-flash-support-from.html&#34; title=&#34;http://avinashkblog.blogspot.com/2010/05/we-are-removing-flash-support-from.html&#34;&gt;http://avinashkblog.blogspot.com/2010/05/we-are-removing-flash-support-from.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today Adobe started a new campaign to the world that they love openness and Apple through essays, ads, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Adobe says:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We love creativity&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We love innovation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We love apps&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We love the web&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We love Flash&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We love our 3 million developers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optical Illusion [HQ] – Crappy malware floating on Facebook!</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-05-02-optical-illusion-hq-crappy-malware-floating-on-facebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-05-02-optical-illusion-hq-crappy-malware-floating-on-facebook/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ok. A bunch of people that are my friends are getting this video posted on their walls, and it looks like porn or something. A lot of my friends have gotten it. Even I allowed it incidentally and it posted on many of my fr’s walls automatically. Its this lower half of a naked girl (nothing shown!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The application seems to be called “Optical Illusion [HQ]’ and if you click on one of the links it will send out the link to people on your friends list stating person’s name, this is without doubt the hottest video ever! :P :P :P and a link.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Remove Farmville like App Notifications on Facebook Wall</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-04-04-how-to-remove-farmville-like-app-notifications-on-facebook-wall/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-04-04-how-to-remove-farmville-like-app-notifications-on-facebook-wall/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Many people want to stop, delete and remove Farmville, Zoo world, Mafia wars like App Notifications, emails, updates, posts on their Facebook wall and news feed. I have so many friends playing these kind of Apps that my FB news feed is full of unwanted crappy updates!&lt;br&gt;
Your friends are addicted Zoo world, Farmville fans and will not stop playing just because you don’t want their FB updates from messaging your wall.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Main Bhi “BABA”</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-03-31-main-bhi-baba/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-03-31-main-bhi-baba/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Avinash’s note:&lt;/strong&gt; This guest post is written by Pooja Bhardwaj. She is a typical Piscean who loves to enjoy each and every min of her life.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Standing near the door, managing myself in half square feet of area, amongst hyperactive women cribbing about mother-in-laws, bitching about “to-be daughter in laws”, at 7 in the morning makes me wonder if a special “Viagara powered women horlicks” is available at the local chemist. You guessed it right, m dragging myself to my office in the mumbai local train.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just installed Fedora9 in a Windows Virtual PC VM for my brother</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-03-21-just-installed-fedora9-in-a-windows-virtual-pc-vm-for-my-brother/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-03-21-just-installed-fedora9-in-a-windows-virtual-pc-vm-for-my-brother/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Just installed Fedora9 in a Windows Virtual PC VM for my brother.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Will it install out of the box if you have .iso Fedora image. The answer is no. When I booted the VM after inserting .iso Fedora image, VPC turned off with error - &amp;lsquo;An unrecoverable processor error has been encountered.  The virtual machine will reset now.&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fortunately, after googling sometime, I came to know that I have to add some parameters &lt;strong&gt;noreplace-paravirt&lt;/strong&gt; to the end of the boot parameters.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>81.25% New Visits increase for my new blog in just 2 days of its launch</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-03-18-81-25-new-visits-increase-for-my-new-blog-in-just-2-days-of-its-launch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-03-18-81-25-new-visits-increase-for-my-new-blog-in-just-2-days-of-its-launch/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;81.25% New Visits increase for my new site &lt;a href=&#34;http://AvinashkBlog.Blogspot.com&#34;&gt;http://AvinashkBlog.Blogspot.com&lt;/a&gt; in just &lt;strong&gt;2 days&lt;/strong&gt; of its launch. Thanks everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is the detailed report:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Site Usage:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/S6JIGiecxxI/AAAAAAAABBY/4pmfzM1LY8g/s1600-h/Site+Usage.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;//localhost:1313/posts/2010-03-18-81-25-new-visits-increase-for-my-new-blog-in-just-2-days-of-its-launch/images/Site+Usage.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More to come:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How this blog evolved?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;More posts in &amp;lsquo;How To&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;Tech News&amp;rsquo; section&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attractive flash home page&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;DNS redirection to a custom URL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Will add some points on the fly (:P)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And lastly Ads&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Leave suggestions in the comment box.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surprise Bday Wish!</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-03-16-surprise-bday-wish/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-03-16-surprise-bday-wish/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After loads of Bday wishes from friends all over the globe over Phone, FB, Orkut, Twitter, Email&amp;hellip;I just returned home and started checking mails on my E63.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One Email really surprised me! My CEO specially sent a Bday wish email :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A big thanks to him and not to forget my boss who reminded the day. I never miss this special one!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who is Avinash Kumpati ?</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-03-16-who-is-avinash-kumpati/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2010-03-16-who-is-avinash-kumpati/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Avinash Kumpati is a fervent IT engineer&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He&amp;rsquo;s been fascinated by technology since youth. He is optimistic and hardworking, easy-going by nature&amp;hellip;loves to dress in style&amp;hellip;populary known as &amp;lsquo;Avi&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And just like every minute is unique, so his innovations are.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
